<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Solve Popular</title>
  
  <subtitle>Enjoy life easier but more creative!</subtitle>
  <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/"/>
  <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.726Z</updated>
  <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Matthew</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Unveiling Process Intelligence: Insights Into Advanced Data Analytics</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/unveiling-process-intelligence-insights-into-advanced-data-analytics/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/unveiling-process-intelligence-insights-into-advanced-data-analytics/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.726Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.726Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Unveiling-Process-Intelligence-Insights-Into-Advanced-Data-Analytics"><a href="#Unveiling-Process-Intelligence-Insights-Into-Advanced-Data-Analytics" class="headerlink" title="Unveiling Process Intelligence: Insights Into Advanced Data Analytics"></a>Unveiling Process Intelligence: Insights Into Advanced Data Analytics</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to ABBYY Blog <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="What-Is-Process-Intelligence"><a href="#What-Is-Process-Intelligence" class="headerlink" title="What Is Process Intelligence?"></a>What Is Process Intelligence?</h2><h6 id="Scott-Opitz"><a href="#Scott-Opitz" class="headerlink" title="Scott Opitz"></a>Scott Opitz</h6><p>October 06, 2023</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/37862/5-pillars-cover-photo_d_848x444-3.jpg"                                     > </p><p>In the current competitive business environment, streamlining and optimizing business processes is crucial for an organization’s success and long-term advantage. However, as the landscape is inundated with promises of digital transformation, many process mining and task mining tools alone fall short of their promise to solve all process-related challenges. These limitations in the first-generation offerings have led to the emergence of comprehensive process intelligence platforms designed to fully meet these demands and go beyond surface-level issues. A true <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >process intelligence solution <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> must fully support five key pillars, which are essential for a holistic approach to process transformation.</p><p>Jump to:</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >What is process intelligence? <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >What are the benefits of process intelligence? <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Use cases <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Pairing process intelligence with IPA <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Frequently asked questions <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="What-is-process-intelligence"><a href="#What-is-process-intelligence" class="headerlink" title="What is process intelligence?"></a>What is process intelligence?</h2><p><strong>Process intelligence is a combination of data-driven capabilities dedicated to the analysis and enhancement of business operations.</strong> It uses the data from a business’ own information systems to uncover patterns and insights that point the way to new operational efficiencies. <strong>The five essential pillars for sustainable process intelligence are process discovery, process analysis, process monitoring, process prediction, and process simulation.</strong> Organizations can use these insights to discover, understand, and manage execution of their processes more effectively.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><h3 id="200610"><a class="link"   href="https://sentrypc.7eer.net/c/5597632/200610/3022" >Parental Control Software <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></h3><span class="text-ad-content">    #1 Rated Parental Control Software.<br/>    Monitor & Control all PC Activity!<br/>        <cite style="color:green">sentrypc.com/parental-controls/</cite>    </span><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://sentrypc.7eer.net/i/5597632/200610/3022"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ><!-- affiliate ads end -->### The five pillars of process intelligence<h4 id="1-Process-Discovery"><a href="#1-Process-Discovery" class="headerlink" title="1. Process Discovery"></a>1. Process Discovery</h4><p>Process discovery is the foundational step in understanding how a process actually operates, comprising <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >process mining <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >task mining <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. Process mining is used for reconstructing processes from events recorded in logs, while task mining fills process gaps by mining user desktop activities. For example, a healthcare provider may use process mining to reconstruct the patient admission process by analyzing the electronic health record (EHR) system’s event logs.</p><p>Simultaneously, task mining can be used to observe and analyze the actions of administrative staff on their desktops to fill in any gaps in the process not captured by the event logs. This comprehensive approach is essential for identifying bottlenecks, redundancies, and deviations, ultimately leading to improved efficiency and patient satisfaction.</p><h4 id="2-Process-analysis"><a href="#2-Process-analysis" class="headerlink" title="2. Process analysis"></a>2. Process analysis</h4><p>Process analysis involves using specialized tools to visualize and analyze process data. For example, an insurance company may use these tools to identify bottlenecks or inefficiencies in its claims processing system. Making these tools accessible to both technical and non-technical users ensures that all stakeholders can participate in the analysis and decision-making process. This fosters a culture of continuous improvement and accountability, leading to faster claims processing, reduced operational costs, and enhanced customer satisfaction.</p><h4 id="3-Process-monitoring"><a href="#3-Process-monitoring" class="headerlink" title="3. Process monitoring"></a>3. Process monitoring</h4><p>Process monitoring allows the user to define specific process patterns that should be detected either when they occur or when they are deviated from, and then either alerts the organization or triggers an action in another system to automatically respond. For example, a bank may define a specific sequence of steps that must be followed when approving a loan. A process monitoring tool will automatically detect whenever this sequence is not followed, allowing the bank to quickly identify and address any deviations. This proactive approach helps minimize risks associated with non-compliance, reduce processing times, and ensure a consistent, high-quality customer experience.</p><h4 id="4-Process-prediction"><a href="#4-Process-prediction" class="headerlink" title="4. Process prediction"></a>4. Process prediction</h4><p>Process prediction uses historical execution patterns to train an artificial intelligence (AI) engine to predict the likely outcome of a process very early on. For example, an insurance company may use this approach to predict the likely outcome of a claim based on historical data. This proactive approach allows the company to address any potential issues early, leading to faster claims resolution, reduced costs, and improved customer satisfaction.</p><h4 id="5-Process-simulation"><a href="#5-Process-simulation" class="headerlink" title="5. Process simulation"></a>5. Process simulation</h4><p>Process simulation provides a mechanism for utilizing process histories to automatically configure a simulation. This model can then be adjusted to reflect any proposed changes to the process or resource allocation, with the goal of understanding the impact of those changes before they are implemented. For example, a bank may use this approach to understand the impact of changing staffing levels in its loan approval department. This helps leaders make informed decisions regarding resource allocation and process changes, ultimately leading to optimized operational efficiency and customer satisfaction.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.iobit.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=1468905&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/184260348236f9554fe9375772ff966e/ascscan_728x90.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="What-are-the-benefits-of-process-intelligence"><a href="#What-are-the-benefits-of-process-intelligence" class="headerlink" title="What are the benefits of process intelligence?"></a>What are the benefits of process intelligence?</h2><p>Traditional approaches to business process improvement rely on manual observations, interviews, and surveys, all of which can be subjective and time-consuming. Process intelligence accesses data from the business’ own systems to drive process optimization and automate the monitoring that enables continuous improvement.</p><p>By leveraging process intelligence, organizations can realize a broad range of benefits, including the following.</p><p><strong>Improved efficiency and productivity.</strong> Process intelligence helps organizations identify bottlenecks, inefficiencies, and redundant steps. By using these insights to optimize their processes, businesses can streamline operations, reduce manual work, and enhance overall efficiency and productivity.</p><p><strong>Data-driven decision making.</strong> By providing valuable insights into how different process execution patterns correlate with specific outcomes, process intelligence enables organizations to make informed choices based on real-time and historical data.</p><p><strong>Enhanced compliance and risk management.</strong> Process intelligence can detect compliance lapses early on and provide tools to rectify issues, reducing the risk of penalties and legal consequences.</p><p><strong>Continuous process improvement.</strong> With process monitoring and analysis, organizations can continuously monitor their processes and identify areas for improvement. This iterative approach allows for ongoing optimization and adaptation to changing business conditions.</p><p><strong>Cost savings.</strong> By identifying and eliminating process inefficiencies, organizations can reduce operational costs. Process intelligence enables cost-effective resource allocation and helps avoid unnecessary expenses associated with manual intervention or errors.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4531356&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/8fdd149fcaa7058caccc9c4ad5b0d89a/products/tss-box.JPG"                      border="0"                >The Tube Sites Submitter is a fast and efficient tool for anyone who needs to upload videos quickly, easily and automatically to hundreds of tube sites in mere minutes . </a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Use-cases-for-process-intelligence"><a href="#Use-cases-for-process-intelligence" class="headerlink" title="Use cases for process intelligence"></a>Use cases for process intelligence</h2><p>In any industry, incorporating <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >process intelligence in a digital transformation strategy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> enables organizations to assess the future impact of proposed changes, manage the transition more effectively, ensure the performance of the implemented automation steps, and provide a feedback loop for continuous improvement. Businesses across industries are using process intelligence to drive results in a variety of use cases.</p><h3 id="Healthcare"><a href="#Healthcare" class="headerlink" title="Healthcare"></a>Healthcare</h3><p>Hospitals and other healthcare providers can leverage process intelligence to improve patient experiences and clinical effectiveness, maintain quality standards, and avoid compliance risks. They can facilitate compliance by monitoring clinical operations in real time, while proactively alerting staff when protocols are not followed, or process deviations are detected.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.advancedwebranking.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4715051&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/14edc6ebfdae2e23bbed83d67f50e983/products/33_awr%20logo.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Banking"><a href="#Banking" class="headerlink" title="Banking"></a>Banking</h3><p>Process intelligence enables banks and other financial institutions to drive digital transformation and support risk and regulatory compliance priorities. They can analyze transaction data in near-real time to improve customer service, increase reporting accuracy, and reduce the risk of costly errors. Process monitoring helps them ensure that SLAs, compliance mandates, and legislative requirements are maintained, reducing the risk of costly mistakes that might otherwise be overlooked.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=174416&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.easygifanimator.net/images/gif-animator.png"                      border="0"                >Easy GIF Animator is a powerful animated GIF editor and the top tool for creating animated pictures, banners, buttons and GIF videos. You get extensive animation editing features, animation effects, unmatched image quality and optimization for the web. No other GIF animation software matches our features and ease of use, that’s why Easy GIF Animator is so popular.</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Insurance"><a href="#Insurance" class="headerlink" title="Insurance"></a>Insurance</h3><p>Insurance companies can use predictive analytics to drive risk evaluation, risk selection, and underwriting decisions. They can improve compliance with automated monitoring and remediation while also realizing productivity gains by enabling straight-through data processing. Process analytics deliver business value for internal staff, contract adjusters, third-party support organizations, and other partners.</p><h2 id="Pairing-process-intelligence-with-intelligent-process-automation"><a href="#Pairing-process-intelligence-with-intelligent-process-automation" class="headerlink" title="Pairing process intelligence with intelligent process automation"></a>Pairing process intelligence with intelligent process automation</h2><p>Digital transformation is the integration of digital technology into all areas of a business, fundamentally changing how it operates and delivers value to its customers. Successful efforts involve a radical rethinking of how an organization uses technology, people, and processes to fundamentally change business performance. <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Intelligent process automation (IPA) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> is at the heart of this transformation. It combines artificial intelligence (AI) and automation to create smart business processes that can adapt and evolve over time.</p><p>Let’s consider a real-world example of a global manufacturing company’s digital transformation journey to improve its operational efficiency and customer satisfaction. The company identified its order-to-cash process as a critical area for improvement.</p><p>Before implementing automation, the company used process mining tools to analyze the current state of order-to-cash processes. The analysis revealed several bottlenecks and inefficiencies in the process, such as manual data entry, multiple handoffs between teams, and lack of standardization in the execution of tasks.</p><p><strong>Insights, all based on hard data that reflects how the company actually operates under real-world conditions, enabled optimizations in the process such as:</strong></p><ul><li>Eliminating unnecessary steps</li><li>Reducing handoffs</li><li>Standardizing the execution of tasks</li></ul><p>After implementing these optimizations, the company implemented an intelligent process automation solution, which included robotic process automation (RPA) bots for data entry and extraction, AI algorithms for decision-making, workflow automation for orchestrating the end-to-end process, and process intelligence tools to monitor performance of the automated process and identify further areas for improvement.</p><h2 id="A-holistic-approach-to-process-intelligence"><a href="#A-holistic-approach-to-process-intelligence" class="headerlink" title="A holistic approach to process intelligence"></a>A holistic approach to process intelligence</h2><p>While many process mining or task mining tools claim to offer comprehensive solutions, they often fall short in addressing the complexities and nuances of real-world processes. A truly effective solution must fully support the five pillars explored above. Only by adopting a holistic approach that encompasses all these aspects can organizations hope to achieve meaningful and sustainable process transformation.</p><p>Organizations worldwide are automating time-consuming, routine business processes to enable workers to concentrate on more important tasks that help grow revenue. With ABBYY Timeline, our <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >process intelligence platform <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, you can improve the future of work. Build on the foundation of process mining, understand the process with advanced analytics, and utilize machine learning to improve and optimize your processes. No other solution offers the same amount of process insight and analytics on one platform.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Request trial <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Frequently-asked-questions"><a href="#Frequently-asked-questions" class="headerlink" title="Frequently asked questions"></a>Frequently asked questions</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >What is process intelligence strategy? <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Process intelligence strategy refers to a systematic approach that organizations use to (1) gain insights into how their business processes execute and (2) use those insights to improve efficiency, optimize operations, and make data-driven decisions. It involves the use of AI-driven technologies and analytical tools to collect, analyze, and visualize business process data so that it can fuel strategic decision making.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >What is the difference between process intelligence and intelligent process automation? <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Process intelligence focuses on gaining insights into existing business processes, with the goal of understanding how processes execute and identifying bottlenecks, inefficiencies, and opportunities for improvement. Intelligent process automation (IPA) focuses on automating and optimizing business processes using advanced technologies such as artificial intelligence (AI) and robotic process automation (RPA). Whereas process intelligence is more concerned with understanding, IPA aims to enhance process efficiency, reduce manual effort, and improve accuracy.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >How is process intelligence better than process mining or task mining alone? <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Process mining and task mining play important roles in process intelligence but can only deliver raw data concerning how a process flows (process mining) or activities performed by users as they move the process forward (task mining). Process intelligence uses data from both process mining and task mining to create a complete picture of the process and deliver insights regarding optimal flows, deviations, and inefficiencies.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >What is the first step in process automation? <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>For a process to be automated successfully, it must first be understood and streamlined. Process intelligence provides the insights decision makers need to understand how their processes execute and resolve inefficiencies before automation comes into play. This first step ensures that time and resources are not wasted in an attempt to automate processes that are inherently inefficient.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/blog/artificial-intelligence-ai/"  title="Artificial Intelligence (AI)">Artificial Intelligence (AI) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Digital Transformation <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Intelligent Automation <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Process Mining <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25562/02a-scottopitz-99x99.png"                      alt="Scott Opitz ABBYY"                ></p><p>Scott Opitz</p><p>Chief Technology Officer at ABBYY</p><p>Scott Opitz is Chief Technology Officer and responsible for the global product strategy and execution. Prior to this, he held the position of Chief Marketing Officer, driving global marketing strategies. He joined ABBYY with the acquisition of TimelinePI, for which he was co-founder, President, and CEO from its inception. In this role, he oversaw the integration of TimelinePI’s process intelligence products (now <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Timeline <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>) into ABBYY’s worldwide sales and distribution channels.</p><p>A 30-year veteran of the computer industry, Scott has founded and built companies in the application integration, business process management, and business intelligence spaces. Scott founded and served as President and Chief Executive Officer of Altosoft Corporation, a business intelligence software company that was ultimately acquired by Kofax. Following the acquisition of Altosoft, Scott served as Senior Vice President &amp; General Manager for Analytics.</p><p>In previous positions, Scott served as Senior Vice President, Worldwide Marketing &amp; Business Development for webMethods (now Software AG), where he was responsible for webMethods’ marketing, business development, and strategic product planning. He joined webMethods as a result of its acquisition of IntelliFrame Corporation, a provider of data integration products and the InVista integrated workflow and BPM platform that he co-founded. Scott has also held numerous executive-level positions in technology, marketing and business development roles for public and private companies.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://purchase.swifdoo.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=38709260&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/8b932759a5a04ddb34bf79e3f9072e4b/products/Product%20box%20white-1024x1024.png"                      border="0"                >SwifDoo PDF Perpetual (2-PC)  Free upgrade. No monthly fees ever. </a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Like-share-or-repost"><a href="#Like-share-or-repost" class="headerlink" title="Like, share or repost"></a>Like, share or repost</h3><p>Share </p><h4 id="Subscribe-for-blog-updates"><a href="#Subscribe-for-blog-updates" class="headerlink" title="Subscribe for blog updates"></a>Subscribe for blog updates</h4><p>First name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Last name</p><p>Query string</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Unveiling-Process-Intelligence-Insights-Into-Advanced-Data-Analytics&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Unveiling-Process-Intelligence-Insights-Into-Advance</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Streamline E-Commerce Success: The Power of Advanced Cookiebot Solutions</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/streamline-e-commerce-success-the-power-of-advanced-cookiebot-solutions/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/streamline-e-commerce-success-the-power-of-advanced-cookiebot-solutions/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.708Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.708Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Streamline-E-Commerce-Success-The-Power-of-Advanced-Cookiebot-Solutions"><a href="#Streamline-E-Commerce-Success-The-Power-of-Advanced-Cookiebot-Solutions" class="headerlink" title="Streamline E-Commerce Success: The Power of Advanced Cookiebot Solutions"></a>Streamline E-Commerce Success: The Power of Advanced Cookiebot Solutions</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Customer stories <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Transportation &amp; Logistics | Accounts Payable Automation</p><h2 id="Rhenus-Logistics-Accelerates-Business-Processes-with-ABBYY-IDP"><a href="#Rhenus-Logistics-Accelerates-Business-Processes-with-ABBYY-IDP" class="headerlink" title="Rhenus Logistics Accelerates Business Processes with ABBYY IDP"></a>Rhenus Logistics Accelerates Business Processes with ABBYY IDP</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/logos-white/abbyy.png?h=40&iar=0&w=120"                      alt="pathner logo"                ></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Customer stories <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Rhenus-Logistics-Accelerates-Business-Processes-with-ABBYY-IDP-1"><a href="#Rhenus-Logistics-Accelerates-Business-Processes-with-ABBYY-IDP-1" class="headerlink" title="Rhenus Logistics Accelerates Business Processes with ABBYY IDP"></a>Rhenus Logistics Accelerates Business Processes with ABBYY IDP</h2><p>Transportation &amp; Logistics | Accounts Payable Automation </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/16262/cs-rhenus-556x303-3.jpg"                                     > </p><h4 id="Customer-Overview"><a href="#Customer-Overview" class="headerlink" title="Customer Overview"></a>Customer Overview</h4><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/15831/rhenus-logo_150x80.jpg"                      alt="Rhenus Assets &amp; Services GmbH &amp; Co. KG"                > </p><table><thead><tr><th>Name</th><th>Rhenus Assets &amp; Services GmbH &amp; Co. KG</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Headquarters</td><td>Holzwickede, Germany</td></tr><tr><td>Industry</td><td>Transport and logistics</td></tr><tr><td>Web</td><td><a class="link"   href="http://www.rhenus.com/" >www.rhenus.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></td></tr></tbody></table><h6 id="CHALLENGE"><a href="#CHALLENGE" class="headerlink" title="CHALLENGE"></a>CHALLENGE</h6><p>Processing different, time-critical documents and invoices for the Rhenus Group’s 80 international sites</p><h6 id="SOLUTION"><a href="#SOLUTION" class="headerlink" title="SOLUTION"></a>SOLUTION</h6><p>Automated capture of all relevant document data using ABBYY FlexiCapture for verification and further processing in the appropriate SAP workflows</p><h6 id="RESULTS"><a href="#RESULTS" class="headerlink" title="RESULTS"></a>RESULTS</h6><ul><li>Fast implementation</li><li>Transparent monitoring</li><li>Efficient processing of up to 1.8 million documents p.a.</li></ul><p>Global transport and logistics service company Rhenus Logistics operates more than 460 sites in more than 40 countries worldwide. Their shared services center (SSC) supports Rhenus’ complex supply chain processes using ABBYY intelligent document processing (IDP) to process up to 1.8 million documents annually from 80 international sites.</p><p> “ABBYY won us over from the very start with an outstanding capture rate and a very good priceperformance ratio. In addition, the expert support made fast implementation possible. Over all, we are extremely satisfied.”</p><p> Thomas Schreiber, Head of Shared Services, Corporate IT, Rhenus Assets &amp; Services</p><h4 id="Challenge"><a href="#Challenge" class="headerlink" title="Challenge"></a>Challenge</h4><p>Up to 1.8 million essential documents are processed each year through Rhenus’ SSC. The majority are time-critical due to the strict deadlines entailed in logistics processes. Documents include purchase invoices, clearing documents, delivery notes, loading records, and order-picking notes. Successful processing requires a high level of control and transparency. One key aspect of this process is ensuring that data is recorded efficiently. To successfully meet these requirements, Rhenus Logistics was looking for:</p><ul><li>Automated capture of all relevant document data</li><li>Efficient, highly accurate verification</li><li>Retention of established processes, including existing automation, in their entirety</li></ul><h4 id="Have-a-task-Let’s-find-a-solution"><a href="#Have-a-task-Let’s-find-a-solution" class="headerlink" title="Have a task? Let’s find a solution"></a>Have a task? Let’s find a solution</h4><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >CONTACT US <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h4 id="Solution"><a href="#Solution" class="headerlink" title="Solution"></a>Solution</h4><p>ABBYY IDP was selected for its high-quality data extraction, flexible and transparent architecture, scalability, and fast implementation options.</p><p>The solution needed to fulfill a wide range of requirements, depending on the type of document, the individual procedures required, and the specific data items. As such, the extraction settings for each scenario were adapted based on test documents in order to make sure they could meet the necessary demands.</p><p>Integrated middleware handles archiving and sends status reports to the various logistics systems and&#x2F;or partners. Now, different departments have direct access to the data and documents they require.</p><p><a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/21380/4-flexicapture.jpg"                      alt="FlexiCapture"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY FlexiCapture <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Read more <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static5.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/14363/13-transportation.jpg"                      alt="Transportation"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Transportation <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Read more <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a href="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/8812/case-study-rhenus-transport-logistics-en.pdf" title="PDF version"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/16261/cs-rhenus-360x162-3.jpg"                      alt="PDF Version"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/8812/case-study-rhenus-transport-logistics-en.pdf"  title="PDF version">PDF version <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/8812/case-study-rhenus-transport-logistics-en.pdf"  title="PDF version">Read more <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h6 id="Like-share-or-repost"><a href="#Like-share-or-repost" class="headerlink" title="Like, share or repost"></a>Like, share or repost</h6><p>Share  True ?  : “” </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >More about ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Find your ABBYY office <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://order.glarysoft.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4535075&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/6734fa703f6633ab896eecbdfad8953a/products/GU-500_672.png"                      border="0"                >Glary Utilities PRO -  Premium all-in-one utility to clean, speed up, maintain and protect your PC</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Ready-to-talk-to-an-expert"><a href="#Ready-to-talk-to-an-expert" class="headerlink" title="Ready to talk to an expert?"></a>Ready to talk to an expert?</h3><p>We’d love to help you along your automation journey.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contact us <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Streamline-E-Commerce-Success-The-Power-of-Advanced-Cookiebot-Solutions&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Streamline-E-Commerce-Success-The-Power-of-Advanc</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Optimized with Advanced Traffic Analysis From Cookiebot</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/optimized-with-advanced-traffic-analysis-from-cookiebot/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/optimized-with-advanced-traffic-analysis-from-cookiebot/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.702Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.702Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Optimized-with-Advanced-Traffic-Analysis-From-Cookiebot"><a href="#Optimized-with-Advanced-Traffic-Analysis-From-Cookiebot" class="headerlink" title="Optimized with Advanced Traffic Analysis From Cookiebot"></a>Optimized with Advanced Traffic Analysis From Cookiebot</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Actualités <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="ABBYY-annonce-une-augmentation-de-25-de-son-chiffre-d’affaires-en-2017"><a href="#ABBYY-annonce-une-augmentation-de-25-de-son-chiffre-d’affaires-en-2017" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY annonce une augmentation de 25 % de son chiffre d’affaires en 2017"></a>ABBYY annonce une augmentation de 25 % de son chiffre d’affaires en 2017</h2><p>14 février 2018</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                                     ></p><h4 id="La-multiplication-des-initiatives-de-transformation-numerique-d’intelligence-artificielle-et-d’automatisation-des-processus-par-la-robotique-favorise-la-croissance"><a href="#La-multiplication-des-initiatives-de-transformation-numerique-d’intelligence-artificielle-et-d’automatisation-des-processus-par-la-robotique-favorise-la-croissance" class="headerlink" title="La multiplication des initiatives de transformation numérique, d’intelligence artificielle et d’automatisation des processus par la robotique favorise la croissance"></a><em>La multiplication des initiatives de transformation numérique, d’intelligence artificielle et d’automatisation des processus par la robotique favorise la croissance</em></h4><p>ABBYY®, fournisseur mondial de solutions de capture de données intelligentes, annonce aujourd’hui ses résultats pour 2017. L’entreprise a enregistré une croissance de 25 % de son chiffre d’affaires, soit la plus forte progression en cinq ans.</p><p>En 2017, ABBYY a développé plusieurs projets de grande ampleur pour sa clientèle d’entreprises basée notamment aux Etats-Unis, en Europe ou en Australie. L’octroi de licences de technologie à des partenaires tels que Fujitsu, Epson, Hewlett Packard Enterprise, RICOH et Xerox est également une source de revenus significative pour l’entreprise.</p><p>La croissance d’ABBYY va de pair avec le développement des marchés liés à la transformation numérique, l’intelligence artificielle (IA) et l’automatisation des processus par la robotique (RPA). L’International Data Corporation (IDC) <a class="link"   href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=IDC_P32575"  title="IDC">prévoit <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> que les dépenses mondiales dans ce type de technologies atteindront 1,3 milliard d’USD en 2018 et conserveront un rythme de croissance soutenu au cours des cinq années à venir. De plus, Gartner <a class="link"   href="https://www.gartner.com/smarterwithgartner/top-trends-in-the-gartner-hype-cycle-for-emerging-technologies-2017/"  title="Gartner">considère <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> l’IA comme la catégorie de technologies la plus disruptive qui, au cours des dix prochaines années, apportera aux entreprises un avantage concurrentiel sans précédent. Selon Forrester, le marché de l’IA <a class="link"   href="https://www.forrester.com/report/The+RPA+Market+Will+Reach+29+Billion+By+2021/-/E-RES137229"  title="Forrester">va décupler <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> pour atteindre 29 milliards d’USD d’ici 2020, tandis que le marché de la RPA doublera pour atteindre 2,4 milliards d’USD. McKinsey <a class="link"   href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/digital-mckinsey/our-insights/where-machines-could-replace-humans-and-where-they-cant-yet"  title="McKinsey">prévoit <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> également que d’ici 2036, près de 50 % des processus métiers seront automatisés.</p><p>« Les entreprises comprennent la nécessité de transformer leur processus pour survivre sur les marchés actuels, avec des clients qui ont <em>une réelle exigence d’immédiateté</em>. Les plateformes et solutions d’intelligence artificielle d’ABBYY leur permettent de réussir leur transformation numérique et leur automatisation des processus aussi aisément que possible. C’est pourquoi nous constatons un intérêt croissant pour notre gamme de produits, » commente Ulf Persson, CEO d’ABBYY. « Les entreprises utilisent nos technologies pour accélérer leurs processus d’intégration et de prise de décision, gérer les risques et extraire des informations pertinentes à partir de vastes quantités de données non structurées. »</p><p>En 2017, des changements organisationnels ont également eu lieu au sein d’ABBYY. Ulf Persson a été nommé CEO en janvier 2017, après avoir été Président du conseil d’administration d’ABBYY et y avoir siégé depuis 2002. En tant que CEO, il a créé une nouvelle structure de management mondiale qui, fin 2017, avait intégré les 16 agences implantées dans 13 pays. De nouvelles fonctions ont aussi été créées et un Chief Innovation Officer a été recruté. Ce nouveau modèle répond aux besoins de l’entreprise dans le monde entier, permet de conserver une marque unifiée et renforce la volonté de fournir des innovations dans le domaine de l’intelligence de contenu pour le marché de la transformation numérique.</p><p><strong>A propos d’ABBYY</strong></p><p>ABBYY est un acteur majeur au niveau mondial pour les technologies et les solutions permettant aux entreprises d’actionner l’information. Notre entreprise définit les standards de la capture de données à l’aide de technologies innovantes reposant sur la linguistique et s’intégrant à l’ensemble du cycle de vie des informations. Les solutions ABBYY permettent d’optimiser les processus commerciaux, d’atténuer les risques, d’accélérer les prises de décision et d’accroître les revenus. Les technologies ABBYY sont utilisées sous licence par certaines des plus grandes entreprises et agences gouvernementales internationales, de même que par des PME et des particuliers. ABBYY Europe GmbH est membre du groupe ABBYY et gère les activités commerciales et marketing en Europe occidentale. Le groupe ABBYY dispose de bureaux en Allemagne, au Royaume-Uni, en France, en Espagne, en Ukraine, à Chypre, en Russie, aux États-Unis, au Canada, aux Émirats Arabes Unis, en Australie, au Japon et à Taïwan. Pour en savoir plus, consultez le site <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/"  title="ABBYY">www.ABBYY.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><em>ABBYY, le logo d’ABBYY et FineReader sont des marques déposées ou des appellations commerciales d’ABBYY Software Ltd. Toutes les autres appellations commerciales appartiennent à leurs propriétaires respectifs.</em></p><p><strong>Pour tout renseignement complémentaire, veuillez contacter :</strong></p><p><strong>ABBYY Europe GmbH</strong><br>Eva-Maria Stanglmayr<br>Landsberger Str. 300<br>80687 Munich, Allemagne<br>Tél : +49 89 69 33 33 0<br>Fax : +49 89 69 33 33 300<br>E-mail : press_<a class="link"   href="mailto:&#x65;&#x75;&#x40;&#97;&#x62;&#x62;&#121;&#x79;&#46;&#x63;&#111;&#109;" >&#x65;&#x75;&#x40;&#97;&#x62;&#x62;&#121;&#x79;&#46;&#x63;&#111;&#109; <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br>Web : <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><strong>Axicom pour ABBYY</strong><br>Agathe Boyé<br>Tél : +33 1 56 02 68 27<br>E-mail : <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >agathe.boye@axicom.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>Maëva Morais<br>Tél : +33 1 56 02 68 26<br>E-mail : <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Maeva.morais@axicom.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=195080&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.blumentals.net/scrwonder/images/screensaver-software.png"                      border="0"                >With Screensaver Wonder you can easily make a screensaver from your own pictures and video files. Create screensavers for your own computer or create standalone, self-installing screensavers for easy sharing with your friends. Together with its sister product Screensaver Factory, Screensaver Wonder is one of the most popular screensaver software products in the world, helping thousands of users decorate their computer screens quickly and easily.</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Optimized-with-Advanced-Traffic-Analysis-From-Cookiebot&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Optimized-with-Advanced-Traffic-Analysis-From-Cookiebot&quot; class=&quot;h</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>NeoML: Discover the Power of ABBYY&#39;s Enrichit and Open-Source Software Capabilities</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/neoml-discover-the-power-of-abbyys-enrichit-and-open-source-software-capabilities/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/neoml-discover-the-power-of-abbyys-enrichit-and-open-source-software-capabilities/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.695Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.695Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="NeoML-Discover-the-Power-of-ABBYY’s-Enrichit-and-Open-Source-Software-Capabilities"><a href="#NeoML-Discover-the-Power-of-ABBYY’s-Enrichit-and-Open-Source-Software-Capabilities" class="headerlink" title="NeoML: Discover the Power of ABBYY’s Enrichit and Open-Source Software Capabilities"></a>NeoML: Discover the Power of ABBYY’s Enrichit and Open-Source Software Capabilities</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Actualités <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="ABBYY-enrichit-sa-bibliotheque-Open-Source-NeoML"><a href="#ABBYY-enrichit-sa-bibliotheque-Open-Source-NeoML" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY enrichit sa bibliothèque Open Source NeoML"></a>ABBYY enrichit sa bibliothèque Open Source NeoML</h2><p>22 juin 2021</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                                     ></p><ul><li><em>NeoML offre des performances accrues de 50 % par rapport aux bibliothèques Open Source de Machine Learning existantes.1</em></li><li><em>Le langage de programmation Python, plus simple à appréhender, est désormais compatible avec NeoML, en plus de C++, Java et Objective-C qui étaient déjà pris en charge.</em></li></ul><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, multinationale spécialisée dans l’intelligence digitale, étend les capacités de <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >NeoML <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, sa bibliothèque de développement Open Source. L’objectif est d’accompagner les développeurs dans le déploiement de nouvelles applications basées sur les technologies liées à l’IA et au Machine Learning. NeoML intègre désormais la prise en charge de Python, le langage de programmation le plus populaire pour l’IA et le Machine Learning. La nouvelle mise à jour de la bibliothèque offre des performances 5 à 10 fois supérieures ainsi que la disponibilité de plus de 20 nouvelles fonctions de Machine Learning, dont 10 nouvelles couches réseau et un algorithme d’optimisation amélioré. De plus, NeoML prend en charge la puce M1 d’Apple et les GPU Intel et le système d’exploitation Linux. Ces améliorations ouvrent les perspectives des développeurs qui peuvent ainsi créer de nouvelles applications alimentées par l’IA.</p><p>Selon une <a class="link"   href="https://www.codingame.com/work/codingame-developer-survey-2020/" >étude <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> publiée en 2020 par CodinGame, Python se hisse au rang de Java des classements trimestriels de RedMonk et est « le langage de programmation le plus aimé ». Python est fréquemment utilisé dans les domaines de l’automatisation et du développement web par de nombreuses entreprises en forte croissance comme Google, Pinterest, Spotify ou Dropbox. Apprécia pour sa versatilité, Python est également adopté par le milieu universitaire pour former les étudiants à la programmation, aux sciences de la donnée ou au Machine Learning. L’intégration de Python devrait ainsi permettre de répondre aux besoins d’une plus ample communauté de développeurs. Par exemple, les acteurs du secteur de la santé peuvent rationaliser leurs processus administratifs, cartographier les maladies infectieuses et personnaliser les traitements médicaux ; les assureurs - calculer les primes de leurs polices.</p><p>Les améliorations apportées à la nouvelle version de NeoML offrent des performances technologiques accrues. De fait, le développement d’algorithmes classiques est 10 fois moins long qu’auparavant et celui de réseaux de neurones artificiels est plus rapide de 30 %. Plus globalement, NeoML est 50 % plus rapide par rapport aux bibliothèques Open Source de Machine Learning existantes. Optimisée pour les environnements multiplateformes, NeoML est adaptée au développement d’applications qui nécessitent une expérience utilisateur fluide et un traitement local des données. De plus, la bibliothèque Open Source d’ABBYY s’intègre parfaitement au sein des environnements Cloud.</p><p><em>« L’Open Source est un puissant moteur d’innovation technologique aujourd’hui. Notre collaboration avec la communauté des développeurs nous permet d’améliorer sans cesse NeoML afin de leur apporter les outils nécessaires au bon développement des technologies de demain. Les possibilités offertes par cette mise à jour conduiront, nous l’espérons, les développeurs à imaginer, créer et mettre en place des initiatives hors du commun à fort impact. Nous invitons les développeurs, scientifiques et universitaires à travers le monde à la rejoindre pour contribuer au développement de la plateforme. »</em>, indique Bruce Orcutt, Senior Vice President of Product Marketing d’ABBYY.</p><p>NeoML a été conçu comme un outil universel permettant aux entreprises de traiter et d’analyser des données dans divers formats comme le texte, l’image ou la vidéo. La plateforme prend en charge les principaux langages de programmation tels que C++, Java, Objective-C. Le réseau de neurones artificiels de NeoML prend en charge plus de 100 types de couches de développement différentes et plus de 20 algorithmes de Machine Learning dont les modèles de classification, de régression et de regroupement. NeoML est multiplateforme (Windows, Linux, macOS, iOS et Android) et optimisée pour les processeurs CPU comme GPU.</p><p>NeoML est disponible sur <a class="link"   href="https://github.com/neoml-lib/neoml" >GitHub <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. La communauté NeoML se compose de développeurs répartis à travers le monde (États-Unis, Canada, Allemagne, Pays-Bas, Brésil, Chine, Inde et Corée du Sud). Les algorithmes sont également utilisés pour le développement des solutions d’ABBYY. L’entreprise offre par ailleurs un accompagnement personnalisé aux développeurs, des rapports d’analyse, des mises à jour régulières et des améliorations de performance. À l’avenir, ABBYY prévoit d’ajouter de nouveaux algorithmes et de nouvelles architectures.</p><ul><li>Pour en apprendre plus sur NeoML, rendez-vous sur : <a class="link"   href="https://github.com/neoml-lib/neoml" >https://github.com/neoml-lib/neoml <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</li><li>Pour en apprendre plus sur les solutions d’intelligence digitale d’ABBYY, rendez-vous sur : <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/" >https://www.abbyy.com/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li></ul><hr><p>1 Selon des tests menés par ABBYY.</p><p><strong>À propos d’ABBYY</strong></p><p>ABBYY permet aux entreprises d’appréhender de manière précise leurs process et contenus via sa plateforme d’<a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >intelligence digitale <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. Les technologies d’ABBYY équipent plus de 5 000 entreprises, dont un grand nombre figurent dans le classement Fortune 500. L’entreprise est reconnue pour ses solutions de pointe dans les domaines du <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Content Intelligence <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> et du <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Process Intelligence <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> qui ont pour vocation d’améliorer l’efficacité, la rentabilité et la compétitivité des entreprises ainsi que l’expérience client. ABBYY possède des bureaux dans 14 pays. Pour davantage d’informations, veuillez consulter le site <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >https://www.abbyy.com/fr <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><strong>Contact presse :</strong></p><p>Bianca Stupp<br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >bianca.stupp@abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>  </p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=35038891&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.dupinout.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/DupInOut-New-Duplicate-Scan-Tab.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;NeoML-Discover-the-Power-of-ABBYY’s-Enrichit-and-Open-Source-Software-Capabilities&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#NeoML-Discover-the-Power-of-ABBYY’s-En</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How to Triumph in Mobile User Onboarding - Your Essential E-Book Resource</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/how-to-triumph-in-mobile-user-onboarding-your-essential-e-book-resource/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/how-to-triumph-in-mobile-user-onboarding-your-essential-e-book-resource/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.689Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.689Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="How-to-Triumph-in-Mobile-User-Onboarding-Your-Essential-E-Book-Resource"><a href="#How-to-Triumph-in-Mobile-User-Onboarding-Your-Essential-E-Book-Resource" class="headerlink" title="How to Triumph in Mobile User Onboarding - Your Essential E-Book Resource"></a>How to Triumph in Mobile User Onboarding - Your Essential E-Book Resource</h2><p>E-Book</p><h2 id="Hurden-beim-mobilen-Kunden-Onboarding-uberwinden"><a href="#Hurden-beim-mobilen-Kunden-Onboarding-uberwinden" class="headerlink" title="Hürden beim mobilen Kunden-Onboarding überwinden"></a>Hürden beim mobilen Kunden-Onboarding überwinden</h2><h3 id="Wie-Sie-ausergewohnliche-Kundenerlebnisse-erzielen-und-sowohl-Kundenwachstum-als-auch-Kundenbindungsrate-erhohen"><a href="#Wie-Sie-ausergewohnliche-Kundenerlebnisse-erzielen-und-sowohl-Kundenwachstum-als-auch-Kundenbindungsrate-erhohen" class="headerlink" title="Wie Sie außergewöhnliche Kundenerlebnisse erzielen und sowohl Kundenwachstum als auch Kundenbindungsrate erhöhen"></a>Wie Sie außergewöhnliche Kundenerlebnisse erzielen und sowohl Kundenwachstum als auch Kundenbindungsrate erhöhen</h3><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/22795/ebook-360x188-de.jpg"                      alt="Mobiles Kunden-Onboarding"                ></p><p>Im heutigen Zeitalter digitaler Geschäftstransformation müssen Unternehmen die Erwartungen ihrer Kunden an einfache und intuitive Möglichkeiten zur Registrierung oder Anmeldung für einen Dienst erfüllen, um die Kundentreue im Rahmen der ersten Berührungspunkte zu stärken und die Kundenbindung zu erhöhen.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://tokenmetrics.sjv.io/c/5597632/1864921/20702" target="_top" id="1864921"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/20702-1864921"                      border="0" alt="" width="1251" height="1042"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Jetzt-herunterladen"><a href="#Jetzt-herunterladen" class="headerlink" title="Jetzt herunterladen!"></a>Jetzt herunterladen!</h3><p>Laden Sie das E-Book herunter und erfahren Sie mehr über folgende Themen:</p><ul><li>Wie sich Investitionen in die CX auf die Rentabilität auswirken</li><li>So erfüllen Sie die Wünsche aller Ihrer Kunden</li><li>Das richtige Erlebnis über den richtigen Kanal liefern</li><li>Was ist die kritischste Phase für die Kundentreue</li><li>Wie Sie das Abwandern von Kunden vermeiden und ein angenehmes Onboarding-Erlebnis schaffen</li></ul><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://appsumo.8odi.net/c/5597632/2082541/7443" target="_top" id="2082541"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/7443-2082541"                      border="0" alt="" width="1200" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://appsumo.8odi.net/i/5597632/2082541/7443"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Danke-fur-Ihr-Interesse-an-ABBYY"><a href="#Danke-fur-Ihr-Interesse-an-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Danke für Ihr Interesse an ABBYY."></a>Danke für Ihr Interesse an ABBYY.</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://digital.abbyy.com/hubfs/content/ebook-breaking-barriers-in-mobile-customer-onboarding-de.pdf"  title="E-Book herunterladen">E-Book herunterladen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/31652/factoids-027-77x77.svg"                      alt="Factoids 027 77X77"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://ursime.pxf.io/c/5597632/2048963/16384" target="_top" id="2048963"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/16384-2048963"                      border="0" alt="" width="1200" height="900"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2048963/16384"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Haben-Sie-Fragen-Kontaktieren-Sie-uns"><a href="#Haben-Sie-Fragen-Kontaktieren-Sie-uns" class="headerlink" title="Haben Sie Fragen? Kontaktieren Sie uns."></a>Haben Sie Fragen? <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Kontaktieren Sie uns. <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></h4><h4 id="Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form"><a href="#Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form" class="headerlink" title="Get your copy by filling in the form."></a>Get your copy by filling in the form.</h4><p>Vorname*</p><p>Nachname*</p><p>E-Mail*</p><p>Land*</p><p>LandAfghanistanAland-InselnAlbanienAlgerienAmerikanisch-SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarktisAntigua und BarbudaArgentinienArmenienArubaAustralienÖsterreichAserbaidschanBahamasBahrainBangladeschBarbadosBelgienBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBolivienBonaireBosnien und HerzegowinaBotsuanaBouvetinselBrasilienBritisches Territorium im Indischen OzeanBritische JungferninselnBrunei DarussalamBulgarienBurkina FasoBurundiKambodschaKamerunKanadaCabo VerdeKaimaninselnZentralafrikanische RepublikTschadChileChinaWeihnachtsinselKokosinselnKolumbienKomorenRepublik KongoDemokratische Republik KongoCookinselnCosta RicaKroatienCuraçaoZypernTschechischeCôte d`IvoireDänemarkDschibutiDominicaDominikanische RepublikEcuadorÄgyptenEl SalvadorÄquatorialguineaEritreaEstlandÄthiopienFalklandinselnFäröerFidschiFinnlandFrankreichFranzösisch-GuayanaFranzösisch-PolynesienFranzösische SüdgebieteGabunGambiaGeorgienDeutschlandGhanaGibraltarGriechenlandGrönlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard und die McDonaldinselnVatikanstadtHondurasHongkongUngarnIslandIndienIndonesienIrakIrlandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaikaJapanJerseyJordanienKasachstanKeniaKiribatiSüdkoreaKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLettlandLibanonLesothoLiberiaLibyenLiechtensteinLitauenLuxemburgMacauMazedonienMadagaskarMalawiMalaysiaMaledivenMaliMaltaMarshall-InselnMartiniqueMauretanienMauritiusMayotteMexikoMikronesienMoldawienMonacoMongoleiMontenegroMontserratMarokkoMosambikMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNiederlandeNiederländische AntillenNeukaledonienNeuseelandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolkinselNördliche MarianenNorwegenOmanPakistanPalauPalästinaPanamaPapua-NeuguineaParaguayPeruPhilippinenPitcairnPolenPortugalPuerto RicoKatarRumänienRuandaWiedervereinigungSt. HelenaSt. Kitts und NevisSt. LuciaSaint-Pierre und MiquelonSt. Vincent und die GrenadinenSaint-BarthélemySaint Martin (französischer Teil)SamoaSan MarinoSão Tomé und PríncipeSaudi-ArabienSenegalSerbienSeychellenSierra LeoneSingapurSt. MartinSlowakeiSlowenienSalomonenSüdafrikaSüdgeorgien und die Südlichen SandwichinselnSüdsudanSpanienSri LankaSurinameSpitzbergen (Norwegen)SwasilandSchwedenSchweizTaiwanTadschikistanTansaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad und TobagoTunesienTürkeiTurks- und CaicosinselnTuvaluUgandaUkraineVereinigte Arabische EmirateGroßbritannienUSAUruguayKleinere amerikanische ÜberseeinselnUsbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamAmerikanische JungferninselnWallis und FutunaWestsaharaSambiaSimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>Ich habe die <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Datenschutzerklärung <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> und die <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie-Richtlinie <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> gelesen und bin damit einverstanden.*</p></li><li><p>Ich bin damit einverstanden, dass ABBYY Solutions Ltd. mich per E-Mail über Neuigkeiten zu Produkten und Technologien von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. informiert sowie Einladungen zu Veranstaltungen und Webinaren und Informationen über Whitepaper und Inhalte zu Produkten und Dienstleistungen von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. an mich sendet.</p></li></ul><p>Mir ist bekannt, dass ich meine Einwilligung jederzeit widerrufen kann, indem ich auf den Link zur Abmeldung in einer von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. erhaltenen E-Mail klicke oder über das <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Datensubjekt-Zugriffsformular von ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Anrede</p><p>Academic Title</p><p>Query string</p><p>Stellen Sie eine Frage, oder beschreiben Sie Ihr Anliegen</p><p>Business Scenario Temp</p><p>City</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Vernetzen Sie sich mit uns</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;How-to-Triumph-in-Mobile-User-Onboarding-Your-Essential-E-Book-Resource&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#How-to-Triumph-in-Mobile-User-Onboarding-Your-Ess</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Enhance Your Data Capture Efficiency: Transitioning to the Advanced ABBYY FlexiCapture Cloud Solution</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/enhance-your-data-capture-efficiency-transitioning-to-the-advanced-abbyy-flexicapture-cloud-solution/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/enhance-your-data-capture-efficiency-transitioning-to-the-advanced-abbyy-flexicapture-cloud-solution/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.681Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.681Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Enhance-Your-Data-Capture-Efficiency-Transitioning-to-the-Advanced-ABBYY-FlexiCapture-Cloud-Solution"><a href="#Enhance-Your-Data-Capture-Efficiency-Transitioning-to-the-Advanced-ABBYY-FlexiCapture-Cloud-Solution" class="headerlink" title="Enhance Your Data Capture Efficiency: Transitioning to the Advanced ABBYY FlexiCapture Cloud Solution"></a>Enhance Your Data Capture Efficiency: Transitioning to the Advanced ABBYY FlexiCapture Cloud Solution</h2><p>ABBYY FlexiCapture Cloud</p><h2 id="Embed-FlexiCapture-Capabilities"><a href="#Embed-FlexiCapture-Capabilities" class="headerlink" title="Embed FlexiCapture Capabilities"></a>Embed FlexiCapture Capabilities</h2><h4 id="Upgrade-procedure"><a href="#Upgrade-procedure" class="headerlink" title="Upgrade procedure"></a>Upgrade procedure</h4><p>We improve our product to deliver the best experience for our users</p><h5 id="Recommended-steps-to-prepare-for-the-update-of-FlexiCapture-Cloud-SaaS"><a href="#Recommended-steps-to-prepare-for-the-update-of-FlexiCapture-Cloud-SaaS" class="headerlink" title="Recommended steps to prepare for the update of FlexiCapture Cloud SaaS"></a>Recommended steps to prepare for the update of FlexiCapture Cloud SaaS</h5><p><strong>Please follow the steps below:</strong></p><ol><li>Validation of your projects and applications in a preproduction environment with the new version FlexiCapture prior to the update is recommended. To request a preproduction tenant please contact your account manager.</li><li>To ensure a quick update of your project, please  <ol><li>remove unused document definitions via Project Setup Station.  </li><li>consider <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >compacting <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> your project to remove unused versions of document definitions. As usual, it is the best practice to validate all changes using a dev&#x2F;test environment before making the changes to your production project.  </li><li>set the retention period for processed batches to a lower value (under 5..7 days).</li></ol></li><li>In case a Document Definition in your production project is locked for editing, all your local changes will be discarded and the document definition will be upgraded automatically. Please check and unlock all document definitions using Project Setup Station (a part of Developer Package) before the upgrade.</li><li>If you use local stations, download the installation images before the actual update.</li><li>Processing of tasks submitted through FlexiCapture Cloud REST API will be suspended for the duration of maintenance window.</li><li>The client using the API should be prepared to retry processing of any failed tasks submitted during the maintenance window or the tasks that didn’t complete processing before the maintenance window.</li><li>If you use FlexiCapture Cloud in several regions, please ensure you have checked the schedule for the maintenance window for each specific region.</li></ol><h5 id="What-you-should-know-about-FlexiCapture-Cloud-SaaS-update-procedure"><a href="#What-you-should-know-about-FlexiCapture-Cloud-SaaS-update-procedure" class="headerlink" title="What you should know about FlexiCapture Cloud SaaS update procedure"></a>What you should know about FlexiCapture Cloud SaaS update procedure</h5><ol><li>The FlexiCapture Cloud update is performed during a scheduled maintenance window. To avoid any problems we recommend that you don’t use the system during the maintenance window.</li><li>The FlexiCapture Cloud Operations team will update all components and services of FlexiCapture Cloud, validate the functionality of the environment and automatically update all projects to allow processing with the latest version of FlexiCapture.</li><li>All tenants in FlexiCapture Cloud will be updated together during the maintenance period.</li><li>Users may be unable to log in to the service for a short period of time.</li><li>Users who are already logged in and are working on the verification tasks will experience errors. Therefore, we recommend that you avoid using the service during the maintenance window.</li><li>The service may fail to accept tasks for processing.</li><li>Processing of tasks submitted through FlexiCapture Cloud REST API will be delayed for the duration of the maintenance window. The client applications using FlexiCapture Cloud REST API must be prepared to retry processing of any failed tasks submitted during the maintenance window.</li><li>Batches that are pending processing or submitted for processing during the maintenance period will go to Exceptions until the corresponding projects are updated. Users may restart processing of the batches that went to Exceptions manually, or submit the batches for processing again.</li><li>The update of all projects for all current customers in the environment will be completed within the maintenance window.</li><li>To continue using local stations (Verification Station, Project Setup Station and others), you must install the new version after the Cloud has been updated. Installation images are available for download at <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com/flexicapture-downloads/cloud/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li></ol><h5 id="Highlights-of-ICaaS-applications-update"><a href="#Highlights-of-ICaaS-applications-update" class="headerlink" title="Highlights of ICaaS applications update"></a>Highlights of ICaaS applications update</h5><ol><li>ICaaS applications and the underlying FlexiCapture Cloud Projects will be updated during a scheduled maintenance window.</li><li>Processing of tasks submitted through ICaaS API will be delayed for the duration of the maintenance window.</li><li>The client applications using ICaaS must be prepared to retry processing of any failed tasks submitted during the maintenance window.</li></ol><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://purchase.swifdoo.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=40002580&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/8b932759a5a04ddb34bf79e3f9072e4b/products/3_Product%20box%20white-1024x1024.png"                      border="0"                >SwifDoo PDF 2-Year Plan</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Enhance-Your-Data-Capture-Efficiency-Transitioning-to-the-Advanced-ABBYY-FlexiCapture-Cloud-Solution&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Enhance-Your-Data-Ca</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Emotional Intelligence</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/emotional-intelligence/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/emotional-intelligence/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.675Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.675Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Emotional-Intelligence"><a href="#Emotional-Intelligence" class="headerlink" title="Emotional Intelligence"></a>Emotional Intelligence</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Newsroom <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="ABBYY-Appoints-Gabrielle-Lukianchuk-as-Chief-Marketing-Officer-to-Accelerate-Growth"><a href="#ABBYY-Appoints-Gabrielle-Lukianchuk-as-Chief-Marketing-Officer-to-Accelerate-Growth" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY Appoints Gabrielle Lukianchuk as Chief Marketing Officer to Accelerate Growth"></a>ABBYY Appoints Gabrielle Lukianchuk as Chief Marketing Officer to Accelerate Growth</h2><p>August 23, 2022</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                      alt="ShutterStock"                ></p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/35915/gabriela-lukianchuck.jpg"                      alt="Gabriela Lukianchuck"                > </p><p>Brand and market accelerator Gabrielle Lukianchuk joins <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> as its new Chief Marketing Officer. Throughout her 25-year career, Lukianchuk has been a pioneer in leading transformative approaches to marketing centered on the customer. Her intentional storytelling approach on a global scale has enabled GTM strategies with measured business impact at technology organizations such as ConvergeOne, Fiserv, ACI Worldwide and CA Technologies&#x2F;Broadcom. As a member of ABBYY’s executive management team, Gabrielle will lead the global marketing function to accelerate the growth of the company’s market leadership in the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >intelligent process automation <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> (IPA) market.</p><p>Gabrielle and her team will be pivotal as we complete our transition to the IPA market. Our ambition to be a leader in this market requires effective market communication and a brand that reflects ABBYY’s innovation and top-quality products. Crucially, Gabrielle will focus on further tightening collaboration with our customers as we help them achieve their intelligent automation goals.  </p><p>Gabrielle’s leadership style, creativity, and metrics-driven approach will significantly impact ABBYY and our customers.</p><p><em>Ulf Persson, Chief Executive Officer at ABBYY.</em></p><p>The ABBYY brand is proven with a 30+ year track record of enabling exponential business growth for our customers globally. I am absolutely thrilled to join the ABBYY team as Chief Marketing Officer to lead marketing efforts globally and build on our strong momentum in today’s intelligent process automation market. The ABBYY team and innovative solutions offer extraordinary opportunities for organizations to embrace working smarter and faster while keeping the focus on delivering superior customer experiences.</p><p><em>Gabrielle Lukianchuk, Chief Marketing Officer at ABBYY.</em></p><p>Lukianchuk holds a Master of Business Administration, in Marketing, from California Lutheran University and a Bachelor of Arts in Music from California State University, Los Angeles. She is a passionate supporter of women’s leadership in technology and diversity.</p><h3 id="About-ABBYY"><a href="#About-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="About ABBYY"></a>About ABBYY</h3><p>ABBYY powers intelligent automation. We reimagine the way people work and how companies accelerate business by delivering the intelligence that fuels automation platforms. Our solutions transform enterprise data and empower you with the insights you need to work smarter and faster. </p><p>We help more than 10,000 companies globally, including many of the Fortune 500, to drive significant impact where it matters most: customer experience, profitability, and competitive advantage.</p><p>ABBYY is a US-based global company with offices in 15 countries. For more information, visit <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com/company/about-us/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and follow us on <a class="link"   href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/abbyy" >LinkedIn <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://twitter.com/ABBYY%5FSoftware" >Twitter <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and <a class="link"   href="https://www.facebook.com/ABBYYsoft" >Facebook <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>ABBYY can either be a registered trademark or a trademark and can also be a logo, a company name (or part of it), or part of a product name of ABBYY group companies and may not be used without consent of its respective owners.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://aofit.pxf.io/c/5597632/1399701/16396" target="_top" id="1399701"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/16396-1399701"                      border="0" alt="" width="960" height="300"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1399701/16396"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Editorial-Contact"><a href="#Editorial-Contact" class="headerlink" title="Editorial Contact"></a>Editorial Contact</h3><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/23662/02d-ginaray.png"                      alt="02D Ginaray"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=2067133&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.pearlmountainsoft.com/n_img/product/gcb/banScrn.jpg"                      border="0"                >Greeting Card Builder</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Gina-Ray-APR"><a href="#Gina-Ray-APR" class="headerlink" title="Gina Ray, APR"></a>Gina Ray, APR</h4><p><em>Director of Global Public Relations</em></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >gina.ray@abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Emotional-Intelligence&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Emotional-Intelligence&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Emotional Intelligence&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Emotional Intelligen</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Digital Twins and Process Simulation - Exploring Business Opportunity Expansion</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/digital-twins-and-process-simulation-exploring-business-opportunity-expansion/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/digital-twins-and-process-simulation-exploring-business-opportunity-expansion/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.669Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.669Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Digital-Twins-and-Process-Simulation-Exploring-Business-Opportunity-Expansion"><a href="#Digital-Twins-and-Process-Simulation-Exploring-Business-Opportunity-Expansion" class="headerlink" title="Digital Twins and Process Simulation - Exploring Business Opportunity Expansion"></a>Digital Twins and Process Simulation - Exploring Business Opportunity Expansion</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Zurück zu ABBYY Blog <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Nutzung-des-Potenzials-digitaler-Zwillinge-mit-Prozesssimulation"><a href="#Nutzung-des-Potenzials-digitaler-Zwillinge-mit-Prozesssimulation" class="headerlink" title="Nutzung des Potenzials digitaler Zwillinge mit Prozesssimulation"></a>Nutzung des Potenzials digitaler Zwillinge mit Prozesssimulation</h2><h6 id="Bruce-Orcutt"><a href="#Bruce-Orcutt" class="headerlink" title="Bruce Orcutt"></a>Bruce Orcutt</h6><p>August 6, 2024</p><p>Der digitale Zwilling, ein Begriff, der in der Geschäftswelt, insbesondere im Bereich der <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Process Mining <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>-Tools, derzeit oft zu hören ist und für Aufregung und immer neue Versprechungen sorgt, ist kein neuartiges Konzept, das über Nacht entstanden ist. Seine Wurzeln reichen weit zurück in die Geschichte der Hightech-Entwicklung, wo digitale Zwillinge seit Jahren pragmatischere Innovationen ermöglichen.</p><p>Gehe direkt zu:</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >3 Wege, wie Prozesssimulation die Verbesserung von Geschäftsprozessen beeinflusst <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Wie Prozesssimulation den Ansatz verschiedener Branchen zur Prozessoptimierung verändert <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Wie Prozesssimulation Patienten und Personal im Gesundheitswesen helfen kann <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Effizienzsteigerung mit digitalen Zwillingen in der Fertigung <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Möglichkeiten zur Nutzung von Prozesserkennung und -simulation im Bankwesen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Optimierung der Prozesse im Online-Handel für mehr Kundenzufriedenheit <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Möchten Sie mehr darüber erfahren, wie Sie Ihre Prozesse mit Prozesssimulation auf die Probe stellen können? <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Denken Sie einmal an die komplizierte Welt der technischen Entwicklung – jedes Düsentriebwerk, jedes Raketenantriebssystem oder jede ähnlich anspruchsvolle Maschine –, in der die Kosten für Prototypen und Tests extrem hoch sind und die Fehlermarge verschwindend gering ist. Hierbei steht extrem viel auf dem Spiel. In diesem Kontext wurde das Konzept des digitalen Zwillings erdacht und perfektioniert, das es Ingenieuren ermöglicht, komplexe Systeme in einer digitalen Umgebung zu entwerfen, zu simulieren und zu verbessern, lange bevor ihre realen Gegenstücke gebaut werden. </p><p>Angesichts der Begeisterung für digitale Zwillinge in der heutigen Geschäftsprozesslandschaft ist es wichtig, dieses reiche Erbe zu erkennen und zu nutzen. Das Versprechen ist verlockend: Wenn Ingenieure die Dynamik eines Düsentriebwerks simulieren können, warum können Unternehmen dann nicht auch ihre Prozesse simulieren und „auf die Probe stellen“, um Kosten zu senken und Risiken zu minimieren? Genau wie ein statischer Entwurf eines Düsentriebwerks ohne Simulationen nur von begrenztem Nutzen ist, so schöpft auch ein digitaler Zwilling eines Geschäftsprozesses ohne integrierte Simulationsfunktionen sein Potenzial nicht voll aus.</p><h3 id="Warum-Prozesssimulation-fur-die-Verbesserung-von-Geschaftsprozessen-wichtig-ist"><a href="#Warum-Prozesssimulation-fur-die-Verbesserung-von-Geschaftsprozessen-wichtig-ist" class="headerlink" title="Warum Prozesssimulation für die Verbesserung von Geschäftsprozessen wichtig ist"></a>Warum Prozesssimulation für die Verbesserung von Geschäftsprozessen wichtig ist</h3><h5 id="Kosteneffizienz"><a href="#Kosteneffizienz" class="headerlink" title="Kosteneffizienz"></a>Kosteneffizienz</h5><p>Genauso wie die Erstellung eines Prototyps für ein neues Flugzeug, der nur auf der Theorie basiert, extrem teuer und riskant sein kann, kann sich auch die Einführung eines neuen oder veränderten Geschäftsprozesses ohne vorherige Bestätigung seiner Leistung unter verschiedenen Simulationsbedingungen als riskant und kostspielig erweisen. Durch die Simulation eines geplanten Geschäftsprozesses kann ein Unternehmen Nacharbeiten zur Korrektur schlechter Leistungen, die von den Prozessdesignern nicht vorhergesehen wurden, und damit die Verschwendung von Humanressourcen vermeiden. </p><h5 id="Risk-reduction"><a href="#Risk-reduction" class="headerlink" title="Risk reduction"></a>Risk reduction</h5><p>In the aerospace industry, a failed engine prototype could mean a loss of billions, not to mention a possible loss of lives. In business, a flawed process could mean decreased productivity, lost customers, or process compliance violations. In the case of processes whose purpose is to serve a human customer in healthcare, public safety, or other high-risk situations, these failures can be even more dire. Simulations allow organizations to identify and rectify potential failures to mitigate these risks. </p><h5 id="Schnelle-Innovation"><a href="#Schnelle-Innovation" class="headerlink" title="Schnelle Innovation"></a>Schnelle Innovation</h5><p>Digitale Zwillinge beschleunigen Innovationen in der Technik, indem sie die zeitaufwändige Phase des physischen Prototypings überflüssig machen. In ähnlicher Weise kann die Simulation bei Geschäftsprozessen Änderungen beschleunigen, indem sie mögliche Ergebnisse sofort aufzeigt. Dadurch werden langwierige Versuchszyklen verkürzt, und die Implementierungsteams können sich ganz auf die Prozessimplementierung konzentrieren, ohne nicht optimale Prozessentwürfe überarbeiten zu müssen. </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/insights/blog/realizing-promise-of-digital-twins-with-process-simulation/process-simulation-image-2024-03-05-23-51-33-401.png?h=477&w=848"                      alt="process-simulation-image"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=37701530&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/6fe0c81e3f9438db11ebbfba6c5ce460/products/copy_cbLogo_with_text_blue.png"                      border="0"                >CalendarBudget - Monthly subscription membership to CalendarBudget via web browser or mobile app. Support included. </a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Beispiele-aus-verschiedenen-Branchen"><a href="#Beispiele-aus-verschiedenen-Branchen" class="headerlink" title="Beispiele aus verschiedenen Branchen"></a>Beispiele aus verschiedenen Branchen</h3><h5 id="Gesundheitswesen"><a href="#Gesundheitswesen" class="headerlink" title="Gesundheitswesen"></a>Gesundheitswesen</h5><p>Nehmen wir ein Krankenhaus, das den Patientenfluss in seiner Notaufnahme optimieren möchte. Durch die Erkundung von Geschäftsprozessen wurde die aktuelle Patientenreise ermittelt. Bevor jedoch Änderungen vorgenommen werden – wie z. B. die Änderung eines Triage-Systems oder der Einsatz von mehr Personal zu Spitzenzeiten –, können verschiedene Szenarien simuliert werden, um durch diese Änderungen verursachte unbeabsichtigte Probleme zu erkennen. So wird sichergestellt, dass die vorgeschlagenen Lösungen nicht ungewollt die Wartezeiten für die Patienten verlängern oder das Personal überlasten. </p><h5 id="Fertigung"><a href="#Fertigung" class="headerlink" title="Fertigung"></a>Fertigung</h5><p>Ein Automobilhersteller möchte die Effizienz seiner Montagelinie verbessern. Mithilfe eines digitalen Prozesszwillings werden Änderungen wie die Neuanordnung von Montagestationen oder die Einführung von Roboterarmen simuliert. Durch Simulationen lässt sich vorhersagen, wie sich diese Änderungen auf Produktionszeiten, Produktqualität und Mitarbeitersicherheit auswirken würden. </p><h5 id="Banken"><a href="#Banken" class="headerlink" title="Banken"></a>Banken</h5><p>Eine Bank möchte ihr Kreditgenehmigungsverfahren beschleunigen. Nachdem der aktuelle Prozess bestimmt und abgebildet wurde, werden verschiedene Änderungen simuliert, wie z. B. die Automatisierung von Kreditprüfungen, die Einführung einer digitalen Dokumentenprüfung oder die Anpassung des geplanten Personalbestands. Die Simulation trägt dazu bei, dass der Prozess zwar schneller wird, aber keine unbeabsichtigten Risiken entstehen, weil die Qualität der erforderlichen Risikobewertungen unbeabsichtigt beeinträchtigt wird. </p><h5 id="E-Commerce"><a href="#E-Commerce" class="headerlink" title="E-Commerce"></a>E-Commerce</h5><p>Ein Online-Händler möchte seinen Produktrückgabeprozess optimieren, um die Kundenzufriedenheit zu erhöhen. Durch die Simulation von Änderungen wie die Einführung von Sofortrückerstattungen, die Vereinfachung von Rücksendeetiketten oder die Bereitstellung von Abholservices lassen sich die Auswirkungen auf Kundenbindung, Betriebskosten und Bestandsverwaltung beurteilen. </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://caperobbin.sjv.io/c/5597632/2006123/18460" target="_top" id="2006123"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/18460-2006123"                      border="0" alt="" width="300" height="250"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2006123/18460"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Prozesse-auf-dem-Prufstand"><a href="#Prozesse-auf-dem-Prufstand" class="headerlink" title="Prozesse auf dem Prüfstand"></a>Prozesse auf dem Prüfstand</h3><p>Die Entwicklung von statischen Konstruktionsplänen hin zu dynamischen digitalen Zwillingen im Ingenieurwesen war ein entscheidender Schritt. Im Bereich der Geschäftsprozesse befinden wir uns an einem ähnlichen Wendepunkt. <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Prozesserkennung <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> liefert eine Blaupause, aber ohne Simulation ist es wie bei einem Düsentriebwerk, das nie unter realen Flugbedingungen getestet wurde. </p><p>Digitale Zwillinge von Prozessen bieten Unternehmen zwar einen einzigartigen Einblick in ihre Abläufe, aber erst Simulationen erschließen ihr transformatives Potenzial. Durch die Erprobung von Änderungen in einer virtuellen Umgebung können Unternehmen Innovationen schneller umsetzen, Risiken reduzieren und Kosteneffizienz gewährleisten. Unabhängig von der Branche verändert die Möglichkeit, per Simulation das volle Potenzial digitaler Zwillinge auszuschöpfen, das Vorgehen bei der Prozessoptimierung. </p><p>Erzählen Sie uns von Ihrem Projekt, indem Sie das Formular ausfüllen und „Prozessintelligenz“ auswählen; wir freuen uns darauf, Sie auf Ihrem Weg der intelligenten Automatisierung zu begleiten. </p><h4 id="Blog-Updates-abbonieren"><a href="#Blog-Updates-abbonieren" class="headerlink" title="Blog Updates abbonieren"></a>Blog Updates abbonieren</h4><p>Vorname*</p><p>E-Mail*</p><p>Land*</p><p>LandAfghanistanAland-InselnAlbanienAlgerienAmerikanisch-SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarktisAntigua und BarbudaArgentinienArmenienArubaAustralienÖsterreichAserbaidschanBahamasBahrainBangladeschBarbadosBelgienBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBolivienBonaireBosnien und HerzegowinaBotsuanaBouvetinselBrasilienBritisches Territorium im Indischen OzeanBritische JungferninselnBrunei DarussalamBulgarienBurkina FasoBurundiKambodschaKamerunKanadaCabo VerdeKaimaninselnZentralafrikanische RepublikTschadChileChinaWeihnachtsinselKokosinselnKolumbienKomorenRepublik KongoDemokratische Republik KongoCookinselnCosta RicaKroatienCuraçaoZypernTschechischeCôte d`IvoireDänemarkDschibutiDominicaDominikanische RepublikEcuadorÄgyptenEl SalvadorÄquatorialguineaEritreaEstlandÄthiopienFalklandinselnFäröerFidschiFinnlandFrankreichFranzösisch-GuayanaFranzösisch-PolynesienFranzösische SüdgebieteGabunGambiaGeorgienDeutschlandGhanaGibraltarGriechenlandGrönlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard und die McDonaldinselnVatikanstadtHondurasHongkongUngarnIslandIndienIndonesienIrakIrlandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaikaJapanJerseyJordanienKasachstanKeniaKiribatiSüdkoreaKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLettlandLibanonLesothoLiberiaLibyenLiechtensteinLitauenLuxemburgMacauMazedonienMadagaskarMalawiMalaysiaMaledivenMaliMaltaMarshall-InselnMartiniqueMauretanienMauritiusMayotteMexikoMikronesienMoldawienMonacoMongoleiMontenegroMontserratMarokkoMosambikMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNiederlandeNiederländische AntillenNeukaledonienNeuseelandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolkinselNördliche MarianenNorwegenOmanPakistanPalauPalästinaPanamaPapua-NeuguineaParaguayPeruPhilippinenPitcairnPolenPortugalPuerto RicoKatarRumänienRuandaWiedervereinigungSt. HelenaSt. Kitts und NevisSt. LuciaSaint-Pierre und MiquelonSt. Vincent und die GrenadinenSaint-BarthélemySaint Martin (französischer Teil)SamoaSan MarinoSão Tomé und PríncipeSaudi-ArabienSenegalSerbienSeychellenSierra LeoneSingapurSt. MartinSlowakeiSlowenienSalomonenSüdafrikaSüdgeorgien und die Südlichen SandwichinselnSüdsudanSpanienSri LankaSurinameSpitzbergen (Norwegen)SwasilandSchwedenSchweizTaiwanTadschikistanTansaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad und TobagoTunesienTürkeiTurks- und CaicosinselnTuvaluUgandaUkraineVereinigte Arabische EmirateGroßbritannienUSAUruguayKleinere amerikanische ÜberseeinselnUsbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamAmerikanische JungferninselnWallis und FutunaWestsaharaSambiaSimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>Ich habe die <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Datenschutzerklärung <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> und die <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie-Richtlinie <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> gelesen und bin damit einverstanden.</p></li><li><p>Ich bin damit einverstanden, dass ABBYY Solutions Ltd. mich per E-Mail über Neuigkeiten zu Produkten und Technologien von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. informiert sowie Einladungen zu Veranstaltungen und Webinaren und Informationen über Whitepaper und Inhalte zu Produkten und Dienstleistungen von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. an mich sendet.</p></li></ul><p>Mir ist bekannt, dass ich meine Einwilligung jederzeit widerrufen kann, indem ich auf den Link zur Abmeldung in einer von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. erhaltenen E-Mail klicke oder über das <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Datensubjekt-Zugriffsformular von ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Nachname</p><p>Query string</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Vernetzen Sie sich mit uns</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Digital-Twins-and-Process-Simulation-Exploring-Business-Opportunity-Expansion&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Digital-Twins-and-Process-Simulation-Explor</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Boosting Productivity - Key Strategies for Your Center of Excellence with ABBYY + Blue Prism Live Session</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/boosting-productivity-key-strategies-for-your-center-of-excellence-with-abbyy-plus-blue-prism-live-session/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/boosting-productivity-key-strategies-for-your-center-of-excellence-with-abbyy-plus-blue-prism-live-session/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.656Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.656Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Boosting-Productivity-Key-Strategies-for-Your-Center-of-Excellence-with-ABBYY-Blue-Prism-Live-Session"><a href="#Boosting-Productivity-Key-Strategies-for-Your-Center-of-Excellence-with-ABBYY-Blue-Prism-Live-Session" class="headerlink" title="Boosting Productivity - Key Strategies for Your Center of Excellence with ABBYY + Blue Prism Live Session"></a>Boosting Productivity - Key Strategies for Your Center of Excellence with ABBYY + Blue Prism Live Session</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Webinars <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="How-Automation-CoEs-are-Realizing-Value-with-Data-Driven-Process-Optimization"><a href="#How-Automation-CoEs-are-Realizing-Value-with-Data-Driven-Process-Optimization" class="headerlink" title="How Automation CoEs are Realizing Value with Data Driven Process Optimization"></a>How Automation CoEs are Realizing Value with Data Driven Process Optimization</h2><p>English</p><h3 id="The-vast-majority-of-process-execution-today-is-tracked-managed-and-performed-through-any-number-of-IT-systems-of-record"><a href="#The-vast-majority-of-process-execution-today-is-tracked-managed-and-performed-through-any-number-of-IT-systems-of-record" class="headerlink" title="The vast majority of process execution today is tracked, managed, and performed through any number of IT systems of record."></a>The vast majority of process execution today is tracked, managed, and performed through any number of IT systems of record.</h3><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/29928/97-how-automation-coes-en-360x232.jpg"                      alt="Webinar on demand: How Automation CoEs are Realizing Value with Data Driven Process Optimization"                ></p><p>That means that organizations already hold a wealth of data about every aspect of their process execution; but are they driving value from it?</p><p>When properly ingested, merged, and analyzed, this wealth of data can be used to discover patterns and insights that illuminate paths to better customer experiences and new operational efficiencies.</p><p>Organizations often struggle with where to start automation projects and how to quantify the value of an RPA project. ABBYY’s Process Intelligence platform delivers that end-to-end system view that provides insight into sources of friction and where the greatest impact of automation resides. By applying advanced artificial intelligence and machine learning, you can predict and forecast processes into the future, while optimizing business operations through real-time monitoring.</p><h3 id="Watch-it-now"><a href="#Watch-it-now" class="headerlink" title="Watch it now!"></a>Watch it now!</h3><p>This session outlines how pharmaceutical giant Pfizer is using ABBYY’s Process Intelligence platform and a proven methodology to build a roadmap for rapid automation across their enterprise utilizing Blue Prism Digital Workers:</p><ul><li>Create a blueprint to drive rapid automation across the enterprise</li><li>Pay for automation with evidenced-base ROI</li><li>Ensure digital workers are operating as expected and providing monitoring and alerts</li><li>Build an automation experience design culture</li><li>Bring business users into the automation journey</li><li>Use Process Intelligence to drive sustainable competitive advantages</li></ul><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4631056&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/997e65474a248252883b485717f7d098/products/buy-windows.png"                      border="0"                >Allavsoft Batch Download Online Videos, Music Offline to MP4, MP3, MOV, etc format </a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Fill-in-the-form-to-register-for-the-webinar-now"><a href="#Fill-in-the-form-to-register-for-the-webinar-now" class="headerlink" title="Fill in the form to register for the webinar now"></a>Fill in the form to register for the webinar now</h3><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://lightailing.sjv.io/c/5597632/1638364/17190" target="_top" id="1638364"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/17190-1638364"                      border="0" alt="" width="1280" height="720"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1638364/17190"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Get-in-touch-with-us"><a href="#Get-in-touch-with-us" class="headerlink" title="Get in touch with us"></a>Get in touch with us</h3><p>Please note that progressive profiling is used on this form to incrementally collect profile data over time.<br>All personal information collected via this method is under full scope of all provisions in our privacy policy.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://turtlebeacheu.sjv.io/c/5597632/1996818/23722" target="_top" id="1996818"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/23722-1996818"                      border="0" alt="" width="600" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1996818/23722"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Thank-you-for-registering"><a href="#Thank-you-for-registering" class="headerlink" title="Thank you for registering!"></a>Thank you for registering!</h2><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aftXSUvP4JU"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static3.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/29882/how-automation-coes-are-realizing-value-with-data-driven-process-optimization.png"                      alt="How Automation Coes Are Realizing Value With Data Driven Process Optimization"                ></a> </p><p>Please check your inbox, we have sent you a confirmation email.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/31652/factoids-027-77x77.svg"                      alt="Factoids 027 77X77"                ></p><h4 id="Have-questions-Contact-ABBYY"><a href="#Have-questions-Contact-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Have questions? Contact ABBYY"></a>Have questions? <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contact ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></h4><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://newchic.sjv.io/c/5597632/1659704/14420" target="_top" id="1659704"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/14420-1659704"                      border="0" alt="" width="728" height="90"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1659704/14420"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="You-might-also-be-interested-in-these-assets"><a href="#You-might-also-be-interested-in-these-assets" class="headerlink" title="You might also be interested in these assets"></a>You might also be interested in these assets</h3><p><a href="https://www.abbyy.com/webinars/on-demand/handelsblatt-podcast-so-klingt-wirtschaft/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/34945/cards-financialservices-360x232.jpg"                      alt="Cards Financialservices 360X232"                > Shared Services &amp; Outsourcing Woche 2021 <img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25122/logo-2021-76x23.svg"                      alt="ABBYY Logo Forcards"                > <img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/35533/fraunhofer-logo-forcards-118x33.png"                      alt="Fraunhofer Logo Forcards 118X33 (1)"                > German Watch webinar</a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://bluettieu.pxf.io/c/5597632/2042323/17091" target="_top" id="2042323"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/17091-2042323"                      border="0" alt="BLUETTI NEW LAUNCH AC180T" width="3840" height="1600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2042323/17091"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p><a href="https://www.abbyy.com/webinars/on-demand/shared-services-and-outsourcing-woche-2021/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static5.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/34944/cards-bpo-360x232.jpg"                      alt="Cards BPO 360X232"                > Shared Services &amp; Outsourcing Woche 2021 <img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/34860/sson-logo-forcards-180x30.png"                      alt="SSON Logo Forcards 180X30"                > <img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static5.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/34858/bosch-logo-forcards-113x27.png"                      alt="Bosch Logo Forcards 113X27"                > <img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25122/logo-2021-76x23.svg"                      alt="ABBYY Logo Forcards"                > German Watch webinar</a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://united.elfm.net/c/5597632/517826/4704" target="_top" id="517826"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/4704-517826"                      border="0" alt="" width="728" height="90"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://united.elfm.net/i/5597632/517826/4704"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Please-fill-in-this-form-to-watch-the-webinar"><a href="#Please-fill-in-this-form-to-watch-the-webinar" class="headerlink" title="Please fill in this form to watch the webinar:"></a>Please fill in this form to watch the webinar:</h4><p>First name*</p><p>Last name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Phone</p><p>Company*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.*</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Query string</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>Business Scenario Temp</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Boosting-Productivity-Key-Strategies-for-Your-Center-of-Excellence-with-ABBYY-Blue-Prism-Live-Session&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Boosting-Productivi</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>ABBYY Welcomes Gabrielle Lukianchuk as New CMO, Driving Company Expansion</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/abbyy-welcomes-gabrielle-lukianchuk-as-new-cmo-driving-company-expansion/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/abbyy-welcomes-gabrielle-lukianchuk-as-new-cmo-driving-company-expansion/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.646Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.646Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="ABBYY-Welcomes-Gabrielle-Lukianchuk-as-New-CMO-Driving-Company-Expansion"><a href="#ABBYY-Welcomes-Gabrielle-Lukianchuk-as-New-CMO-Driving-Company-Expansion" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY Welcomes Gabrielle Lukianchuk as New CMO, Driving Company Expansion"></a>ABBYY Welcomes Gabrielle Lukianchuk as New CMO, Driving Company Expansion</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Newsroom <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="ABBYY-Appoints-Gabrielle-Lukianchuk-as-Chief-Marketing-Officer-to-Accelerate-Growth"><a href="#ABBYY-Appoints-Gabrielle-Lukianchuk-as-Chief-Marketing-Officer-to-Accelerate-Growth" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY Appoints Gabrielle Lukianchuk as Chief Marketing Officer to Accelerate Growth"></a>ABBYY Appoints Gabrielle Lukianchuk as Chief Marketing Officer to Accelerate Growth</h2><p>August 23, 2022</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                      alt="ShutterStock"                ></p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/35915/gabriela-lukianchuck.jpg"                      alt="Gabriela Lukianchuck"                > </p><p>Brand and market accelerator Gabrielle Lukianchuk joins <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> as its new Chief Marketing Officer. Throughout her 25-year career, Lukianchuk has been a pioneer in leading transformative approaches to marketing centered on the customer. Her intentional storytelling approach on a global scale has enabled GTM strategies with measured business impact at technology organizations such as ConvergeOne, Fiserv, ACI Worldwide and CA Technologies&#x2F;Broadcom. As a member of ABBYY’s executive management team, Gabrielle will lead the global marketing function to accelerate the growth of the company’s market leadership in the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >intelligent process automation <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> (IPA) market.</p><p>Gabrielle and her team will be pivotal as we complete our transition to the IPA market. Our ambition to be a leader in this market requires effective market communication and a brand that reflects ABBYY’s innovation and top-quality products. Crucially, Gabrielle will focus on further tightening collaboration with our customers as we help them achieve their intelligent automation goals.  </p><p>Gabrielle’s leadership style, creativity, and metrics-driven approach will significantly impact ABBYY and our customers.</p><p><em>Ulf Persson, Chief Executive Officer at ABBYY.</em></p><p>The ABBYY brand is proven with a 30+ year track record of enabling exponential business growth for our customers globally. I am absolutely thrilled to join the ABBYY team as Chief Marketing Officer to lead marketing efforts globally and build on our strong momentum in today’s intelligent process automation market. The ABBYY team and innovative solutions offer extraordinary opportunities for organizations to embrace working smarter and faster while keeping the focus on delivering superior customer experiences.</p><p><em>Gabrielle Lukianchuk, Chief Marketing Officer at ABBYY.</em></p><p>Lukianchuk holds a Master of Business Administration, in Marketing, from California Lutheran University and a Bachelor of Arts in Music from California State University, Los Angeles. She is a passionate supporter of women’s leadership in technology and diversity.</p><h3 id="About-ABBYY"><a href="#About-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="About ABBYY"></a>About ABBYY</h3><p>ABBYY powers intelligent automation. We reimagine the way people work and how companies accelerate business by delivering the intelligence that fuels automation platforms. Our solutions transform enterprise data and empower you with the insights you need to work smarter and faster. </p><p>We help more than 10,000 companies globally, including many of the Fortune 500, to drive significant impact where it matters most: customer experience, profitability, and competitive advantage.</p><p>ABBYY is a US-based global company with offices in 15 countries. For more information, visit <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com/company/about-us/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and follow us on <a class="link"   href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/abbyy" >LinkedIn <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://twitter.com/ABBYY%5FSoftware" >Twitter <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and <a class="link"   href="https://www.facebook.com/ABBYYsoft" >Facebook <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>ABBYY can either be a registered trademark or a trademark and can also be a logo, a company name (or part of it), or part of a product name of ABBYY group companies and may not be used without consent of its respective owners.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://ukaidot.sjv.io/c/5597632/1793233/19578" target="_top" id="1793233"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/19578-1793233"                      border="0" alt="" width="1200" height="1200"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1793233/19578"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Editorial-Contact"><a href="#Editorial-Contact" class="headerlink" title="Editorial Contact"></a>Editorial Contact</h3><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/23662/02d-ginaray.png"                      alt="02D Ginaray"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4721564&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/c14a8df1e1b4d5297e9cb30cb34d5a00/products/copy_power-tools-48.png"                      border="0"                >Power Tools add-on for Google Sheets, 12-month subscription</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Gina-Ray-APR"><a href="#Gina-Ray-APR" class="headerlink" title="Gina Ray, APR"></a>Gina Ray, APR</h4><p><em>Director of Global Public Relations</em></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >gina.ray@abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;ABBYY-Welcomes-Gabrielle-Lukianchuk-as-New-CMO-Driving-Company-Expansion&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#ABBYY-Welcomes-Gabrielle-Lukianchuk-as-New-CMO-D</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Vereinheitlichte Buchhalterlösungen Mit IGuana Und ABBYY Für Verbesserte Kreditorenverwaltung &amp; Geschäftsprozesse</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/vereinheitlichte-buchhalterlosungen-mit-iguana-und-abbyy-fur-verbesserte-kreditorenverwaltung-and-geschaftsprozesse/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/vereinheitlichte-buchhalterlosungen-mit-iguana-und-abbyy-fur-verbesserte-kreditorenverwaltung-and-geschaftsprozesse/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.640Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.640Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Vereinheitlichte-Buchhalterlosungen-Mit-IGuana-Und-ABBYY-Fur-Verbesserte-Kreditorenverwaltung-Geschaftsprozesse"><a href="#Vereinheitlichte-Buchhalterlosungen-Mit-IGuana-Und-ABBYY-Fur-Verbesserte-Kreditorenverwaltung-Geschaftsprozesse" class="headerlink" title="Vereinheitlichte Buchhalterlösungen Mit IGuana Und ABBYY Für Verbesserte Kreditorenverwaltung &amp; Geschäftsprozesse"></a>Vereinheitlichte Buchhalterlösungen Mit IGuana Und ABBYY Für Verbesserte Kreditorenverwaltung &amp; Geschäftsprozesse</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Newsroom <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="iGuana-und-ABBYY-tun-sich-zusammen-um-Unternehmen-bei-der-Optimierung-und-Automatisierung-von-Prozessen-in-der-Kreditorenbuchhaltung-zu-helfen"><a href="#iGuana-und-ABBYY-tun-sich-zusammen-um-Unternehmen-bei-der-Optimierung-und-Automatisierung-von-Prozessen-in-der-Kreditorenbuchhaltung-zu-helfen" class="headerlink" title="iGuana und ABBYY tun sich zusammen, um Unternehmen bei der Optimierung und Automatisierung von Prozessen in der Kreditorenbuchhaltung zu helfen"></a>iGuana und ABBYY tun sich zusammen, um Unternehmen bei der Optimierung und Automatisierung von Prozessen in der Kreditorenbuchhaltung zu helfen</h2><p>9. Mai 2018</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                                     ></p><p>ABBYY, ein führender, globaler Anbieter von Technologien und Lösungen für den effektiven Einsatz von Informationen in Organisationen, und <a class="link"   href="https://iguana-idm.com/de"  title="iGuana">iGuana <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, ein führender Anbieter von digitalen Archivierungs- und Dokumentenmanagementlösungen, freuen sich, ihre Partnerschaft bekanntzugeben.</p><p>iGuana und ABBYY haben beschlossen, sich zusammenzutun, um Unternehmenskunden bei der Optimierung und Automatisierung der Rechnungsverarbeitung in der Kreditorenbuchhaltung zu unterstützen. Hauptziel der Partnerschaft ist die Integration von zwei leistungsstarken Unternehmenssoftware-Plattformen in eine „One-Stop-Shop-Lösung“ für die automatisierte Erfassung, Datenextraktion, intelligente Verarbeitung und digitale Archivierung von Rechnungen.</p><p>Die Lösung bietet ein beträchtliches Potenzial für unmittelbare Kosteneinsparungen und einen schnellen Return on Investment. Damit kann die Kreditorenbuchhaltung, traditionell ein Cost-Center, in ein Profit-Center umgewandelt werden, das positiv zum Ergebnis des Unternehmens beiträgt. Durch das Scannen von Papierrechnungen an der Eingangsstelle lässt sich ein vollständig automatisierter Buchhaltungsprozess erreichen, beginnend bei der Extraktion von Rechnungsdaten bis hin zur Archivierung der Dokumente nach geltenden Vorschriften.</p><p>Indem sie jahrzehntelange Erfahrung mit elektronischem Dokumentenmanagement, digitaler Archivierung und intelligenter Datenerfassung in vielen Schlüsselindustrien kombinieren, sind iGuana und ABBYY in der Lage, auf die komplexen Bedürfnisse bei der Rechnungsverarbeitung von Unternehmenskunden im Bank-, Finanz-, Versicherungs- und Gesundheitswesen sowie in anderen Branchen einzugehen.</p><p><strong>Die integrierte Rechnungsverarbeitungslösung von iGuana und ABBYY</strong></p><p>Die Verarbeitung von Papierrechnungen ist eine große Herausforderung für Unternehmen. Dieser zeitaufwendige, arbeitsintensive und häufig fehleranfällige Prozess kann sich beträchtlich auf das Ergebnis eines Unternehmens und seine Fähigkeit auswirken, in der heutigen, schnelllebigen Geschäftswelt wettbewerbsfähig zu bleiben.</p><p>ABBYY FlexiCapture, eine Enterprise-Capture-Plattform für Unternehmen, wurde optimal in das elektronische System für Datenmanagement und digitale Archivierung iGuana iDM integriert und kann diese Herausforderung im vollen Umfang bewältigen. Die integrierte Rechnungsverarbeitungslösung von iGuana und ABBYY ermöglicht Unternehmen, eingehende Rechnungen in allen Verarbeitungsschritten der Kreditorenbuchhaltung zu bearbeiten, vom Digitalisieren&#x2F;Scannen und Klassifizieren von Rechnungen, über Datenextraktion und Validierung bis hin zur Genehmigung und Verbuchung von Rechnungsdaten im ERP, in der Buchhaltungssoftware oder jedem anderen Back-End-System.</p><p><strong>Scannen von Rechnungen und Datenextraktion</strong></p><p>Alle eingehenden Papierrechnungen werden direkt in iGuana iDM, ein zentrales digitales Archiv, gescannt. ABBYYs Datenextraktionstechnologie auf der Basis von künstlicher Intelligenz (KI) extrahiert automatisch wichtige Rechnungsdaten (Lieferantenname, Rechnungsnummer, Datum, Betrag und andere). Integrierte länderspezifische Einstellungen erledigen die automatisierte Compliance-Prüfung. Validierte Rechnungen werden automatisch im ERP oder der Buchhaltungssoftware verbucht.</p><p><strong>Rechnungsweiterleitung und Workflow</strong></p><p>Gebuchte Rechnungen können automatisch zur Weiterbearbeitung an verantwortliche Mitarbeiter weitergeleitet werden. Auf Basis von Triggern, Benutzeraktionen und anderen Unternehmensregeln, darunter Rechnungsfreigabe, Eskalation und Fehlerbearbeitung, können Rechnungen auch einen besonderen Workflow durchlaufen. Im Rahmen des Freigabe-Workflows, bei dem bestimmte Anwender bestimmte Handlungen in einer vordefinierten Abfolge vornehmen müssen, können Rechnungen mit speziellen Rechnungsposten beispielsweise automatisch an ausgewählte Anwender weitergeleitet werden. Der Rechnungsstatus wird im ERP oder der Buchhaltungssoftware automatisch aktualisiert, zum Beispiel „Pending Approval“ (Freigabe steht aus). Für alle einzelnen Rechnungstransaktionen ist ein vollständiger Auditbericht verfügbar. Diese Workflow-Aktionen können mithilfe der sicheren Mobil-Anwendung iGuana iDM auch unterwegs ausgeführt werden.</p><p><strong>Rechnungsarchivierung</strong></p><p>Alle gescannten Rechnungen werden indexiert, nach einer logischen Struktur klassifiziert und in iGuana iDM sicher und in einem gesetzeskonformen und revisionssicheren Format archiviert. Mit einer leistungsstarken Suchfunktion können Anwender die Rechnungen einfach bei Bedarf aufrufen, wobei sie alle Rechnungen direkt in ihrem ERP-Fenster ansehen können.</p><p><strong>Wichtige Vorteile</strong></p><p>Die Zusammenarbeit von iGuana und ABBYY macht es möglich, Unternehmenskunden eine einfache und leistungsstarke schlüsselfertige Lösung für die Automatisierung der Kreditorenbuchhaltung anzubieten, die auf einer einzigartigen Kombination aus Erfahrungen mit der Verarbeitung großer Datenmengen und mit intelligenter Datenextraktion beruht.</p><p>Zu den wichtigsten Vorteilen für Kunden gehören unter anderem:</p><ul><li>Höhere Prozesstransparenz und verbesserte interne Kontrollen</li><li>Standardisierung der Rechnungsverarbeitung und -sichtbarkeit für Budgetmanagement und Planung</li><li>Kosteneinsparungen, weil automatisierte Datenextraktion die manuelle Dateneingabe unnötig macht</li><li>Minimieren der Risiken aufgrund von verlorenen, verlegten oder falsch bearbeiteten Rechnungen</li><li>Optimierung der Daten- und Prozessqualität durch Validierung und Sicherstellen der Gesetzeskonformität</li><li>Verbessertes Cashflow-Management durch Vermeiden von Säumniszuschlägen und Doppelzahlungen</li></ul><p><strong>Über iGuana</strong></p><p>iGuana ist ein führender Anbieter von elektronischen Lösungen für das Dokumentenmanagement und Scanserviceleistungen in den Beneluxstaaten. Dank mehr als 30 Jahren Erfahrung hilft iGuana Unternehmen dabei, all ihre Dokumente elektronisch, effizient und gesetzeskonform zu verwalten. iGuana hat seinen Hauptsitz in Belgien und regionale Niederlassungen in den Niederlanden, Luxemburg und Zypern. Das Unternehmen bietet branchenspezifische Lösungen und Dienstleistungen für Konzerne und KMUs in der Finanz-, Bank-, Versicherungs- und Logistikbranche, der Automobilindustrie und anderen Branchen sowie für den öffentlichen Sektor. Bei Lösungen für das Gesundheitswesen ist iGuana Marktführer.</p><p><strong>Über ABBYY</strong></p><p>Action information – ABBYY ist ein führender und globaler Anbieter von Technologien und Lösungen für den effektiven Einsatz von Informationen in Organisationen. Das Unternehmen setzt Maßstäbe für Content Capture sowie für innovative, sprachbasierte Technologien, die sich in den gesamten Informationslebenszyklus integrieren lassen. Durch ABBYY Lösungen lassen sich Geschäftsprozesse optimieren, Risiken mindern, Entscheidungen beschleunigen und Umsätze steigern. ABBYY Technologien werden von einigen der größten internationalen Firmen, öffentlichen Institutionen und Behörden, aber auch von kleinen und mittelständischen Unternehmen sowie Einzelanwendern genutzt. Die ABBYY Europe GmbH ist als Teil der ABBYY Gruppe verantwortlich für Vertrieb und Marketing in Westeuropa. ABBYY unterhält regionale Niederlassungen in Deutschland, Großbritannien, Frankreich, Spanien, den USA, Kanada, Ukraine, Zypern, Russland, den Vereinigten Arabischen Emiraten, Australien, Japan und Taiwan. Weitere Informationen finden Sie im Web unter <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.ABBYY.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><em>ABBYY, das ABBYY Logo und FlexiCapture sind entweder registrierte Warenzeichen oder Warenzeichen von ABBYY Software Ltd. Alle anderen Warenzeichen sind Eigentum ihrer jeweiligen Inhaber.</em></p><p><strong>Für weitere Informationen wenden Sie sich bitte an:</strong></p><p>iGuana NV<br>Leuvensesteenweg 633<br>1930 Zaventem – Belgien<br>Tel.: +32 2 70 90 100<br>E-Mail: <a class="link"   href="mailto:&#105;&#x67;&#x75;&#97;&#110;&#97;&#64;&#105;&#x67;&#117;&#97;&#110;&#x61;&#45;&#100;&#109;&#115;&#46;&#x63;&#111;&#x6d;" >&#105;&#x67;&#x75;&#97;&#110;&#97;&#64;&#105;&#x67;&#117;&#97;&#110;&#x61;&#45;&#100;&#109;&#115;&#46;&#x63;&#111;&#x6d; <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br>Internet: <a class="link"   href="https://iguana-idm.com/de/"  title="iGuana">https://iguana-idm.com/de/ <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>oder</p><p>ABBYY Europe GmbH<br>Christian Schwarzmann<br>Landsberger Straße 300<br>80687 München, Deutschland<br>Tel.: +49 89 69 33 33 0<br>Fax: +49 89 69 33 33 300<br>E-Mail: press_<a class="link"   href="mailto:&#x65;&#x75;&#x40;&#97;&#x62;&#98;&#121;&#x79;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#109;" >&#x65;&#x75;&#x40;&#97;&#x62;&#98;&#121;&#x79;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#109; <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br>Web: <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Pressekontakt:</p><p>LEWIS PR<br>Anna Frank<br>Karlstr. 64<br>D - 80335 München<br>Tel.: +49 89 17 30 19 24<br>E-Mail: <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >abbyygermany@teamlewis.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Vernetzen Sie sich mit uns</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4537546&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/4b0a0290ad7df100b77e86839989a75e/products/7_copy_2_2_hdpro.png"                      border="0"                >HD Video Converter Factory Pro</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Vereinheitlichte-Buchhalterlosungen-Mit-IGuana-Und-ABBYY-Fur-Verbesserte-Kreditorenverwaltung-Geschaftsprozesse&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Vereinhei</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Utilizing Cookiebot Technology for Optimized Web Analytics &amp; Performance</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/utilizing-cookiebot-technology-for-optimized-web-analytics-and-performance/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/utilizing-cookiebot-technology-for-optimized-web-analytics-and-performance/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.627Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.627Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Utilizing-Cookiebot-Technology-for-Optimized-Web-Analytics-Performance"><a href="#Utilizing-Cookiebot-Technology-for-Optimized-Web-Analytics-Performance" class="headerlink" title="Utilizing Cookiebot Technology for Optimized Web Analytics &amp; Performance"></a>Utilizing Cookiebot Technology for Optimized Web Analytics &amp; Performance</h2><p>ABBYY EULA</p><h2 id="Notices"><a href="#Notices" class="headerlink" title="Notices"></a>Notices</h2><ul><li><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >EULA <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >EULA rules for ABBYY Entity, Venue, Governing Laws and Notice Address <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >EULA Notices <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li><li><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Third-Party Technologies <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></li></ul><p>This is a page where ABBYY provides notices under the EULA. There is no actual notice at the moment. It is recommended to check this page regularly for possible notices further on.</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4718728&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"> <img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/ce9a6fb2becc2d235e62b125e9260102/products/vMixCallScreenshot1-large.jpg"                      border="0"                > vMix Basic HD - Software based live production. vMix Basic HD includes 4 inputs, 3 cameras, streaming, recording, playlist.<br>This bundle includes Studio 200 for vMix from Virtualsetworks, HTTP Matrix 1.0 automation scheduler, and 4 introductory training videos from the Udemy vMix Basic to Amazing course. </a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Utilizing-Cookiebot-Technology-for-Optimized-Web-Analytics-Performance&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Utilizing-Cookiebot-Technology-for-Optimized-Web-A</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Understanding The Complexities in Organizational Process Management – Lessons From the ABBYY Blog</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/understanding-the-complexities-in-organizational-process-management-lessons-from-the-abbyy-blog/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/understanding-the-complexities-in-organizational-process-management-lessons-from-the-abbyy-blog/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.624Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.624Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Understanding-The-Complexities-in-Organizational-Process-Management-–-Lessons-From-the-ABBYY-Blog"><a href="#Understanding-The-Complexities-in-Organizational-Process-Management-–-Lessons-From-the-ABBYY-Blog" class="headerlink" title="Understanding The Complexities in Organizational Process Management – Lessons From the ABBYY Blog"></a>Understanding The Complexities in Organizational Process Management – Lessons From the ABBYY Blog</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to ABBYY Blog <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="Why-Process-is-Such-a-Big-Problem"><a href="#Why-Process-is-Such-a-Big-Problem" class="headerlink" title="Why Process is Such a Big Problem"></a>Why Process is Such a Big Problem</h2><h6 id="Reginald-J-Twigg"><a href="#Reginald-J-Twigg" class="headerlink" title="Reginald J. Twigg"></a>Reginald J. Twigg</h6><p>June 15, 2020</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/28766/ocrsdk-visual-default.jpg"                      alt="abbyy cloud ocr sdk | ABBYY Blog Post"                > </p><p>A recent <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >survey <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> commissioned by ABBYY asked decision makers across multiple industries – Financial Services, Insurance, Government, for example – how consistently they believed workers followed processes. As one would expect with any survey, results varied by industry, with Financial Services and Insurance scoring pretty high, but most surprising was the comparatively lower scores Government decision makers (leaders) gave their organizations. Specifically, as aggregated across government sectors surveyed (Federal, State, Local), only 15% of leaders believed their staff followed business processes “rigorously” and 30% believed they “sometimes” followed the rules.</p><p>The true insights to be gained from this survey are not in pitting one industry’s score against the others but to underscore the fact that ‘process’ continues to be a major problem for industry leaders. Especially problematic, but seldom actually examined, is how well staff – knowledge workers in particular – follow processes or work around them. We can look at the usual causes – old technology, inadequate budget, need to modernize or add more automation – all of which have been a boon for technology providers but have failed to address the problem in any meaningful way.</p><h2 id="Perhaps-it’s-time-to-start-looking-at-the-‘process-problem’-differently"><a href="#Perhaps-it’s-time-to-start-looking-at-the-‘process-problem’-differently" class="headerlink" title="Perhaps it’s time to start looking at the ‘process problem’ differently?"></a>Perhaps it’s time to start looking at the ‘process problem’ differently?</h2><p>Government leaders are not unique but make clear what needs to be front and center of conversations about process: people. Processes are made to make people more productive, consistent and accountable, yet they so often are designed and budgeted around data, workflow, training technologies and not on usability. Government workers are knowledge workers, dedicated to solving problems for their constituents. In this context, the data reveal that the three most cited reasons why staff did not follow processes were to meet customer needs (44%), processes are too complex (38%) and not enough time to follow them (31%). This indicates that government employees are willing to take shortcuts in order to meet constituents’ expectations because the <em>processes aren’t working for them</em>.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4718728&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"> <img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/ce9a6fb2becc2d235e62b125e9260102/products/vMixCallScreenshot1-large.jpg"                      border="0"                > vMix Basic HD - Software based live production. vMix Basic HD includes 4 inputs, 3 cameras, streaming, recording, playlist.<br>This bundle includes Studio 200 for vMix from Virtualsetworks, HTTP Matrix 1.0 automation scheduler, and 4 introductory training videos from the Udemy vMix Basic to Amazing course. </a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="A-Different-Look-at-Process-Mining-and-Automation"><a href="#A-Different-Look-at-Process-Mining-and-Automation" class="headerlink" title="A Different Look at Process, Mining and Automation"></a>A Different Look at Process, Mining and Automation</h2><p>With the widespread adoption of robotic process automation (RPA) tools, a new wave of intelligent document processing and OCR tools, and with growing frequency, Process Mining, comes the expectation that processes can be made to work better with the right technologies. That is true to a point, but if those tools are not deployed with honest understanding of how people – knowledge workers in particular – rely on and use processes to assist their productivity, the results of such investments will be the same as with past technology trends. Instead, looking at processes not just as workflows of events and data but as <em>interactions</em> between people, processes and content can yield a better approach.</p><p><em>Government workers, as a case in point,</em> are case workers who have to make decisions and expert determinations on constituent needs based upon the information gathered in their interactions. This information is gathered from conversations and supporting documents. But their processes are about constantly reviewing these needs and making experienced expert decisions about what the best course of action needs to be. Data automation tools can help with the tasks of collecting, organizing and processing documents and creating workflows for automating steps, but they cannot replace the decision-making and actions knowledge workers need to deliver to their clients. Most process mining approaches are designed to discover the flow of data, events, exceptions and resolutions occur but do not show the knowledge worker behaviors, decision factors and how they use content to inform them.</p><p><em>Process Intelligence</em> is an innovative approach to mining processes to show and understand how humans (knowledge workers and clients) actually interact with them, along with the content needed to make decisions and take actions. Using an organization’s data, but examining it in different ways to show the worker or client’s journey through the processes can reveal time on task, bottlenecks, repetitions, workarounds (where humans have to step out of defined process to get the job done). Oftentimes, bottlenecks occur when a knowledge worker has to review and make decisions on the case, looking at supporting documents and gathering more information.</p><p><a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/29019/11982_infographics_process-mining_abbyy-survey_eng_300dpi-5.jpg"                      alt="Infographic of Process Mining ABBYY Survey Results July 2020"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://printrendy.pxf.io/c/5597632/1453720/17020" target="_top" id="1453720"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/17020-1453720"                      border="0" alt="" width="300" height="250"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1453720/17020"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p>The data shown here illustrate that government workers do not get adequate decision and action support from their existing processes and systems to facilitate resolution fast enough, so they ‘go around them.’ Not unique to government, the primary reason why so many process automation solutions are failing (RPA, for example, where it is recognized that over 65% of these implementations are failing to achieve their goals) is because they do not adequately address how knowledge workers do their jobs. Process mining can be part of the same problem if it does not focus on work journeys.</p><p>Solutions such as <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Process Intelligence <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> enable organizations to discover, assess, visualize, analyze, and monitor process flows as interactions between people, processes and content. Powered by artificial intelligence and machine learning technologies, Process Intelligence delivers accurate, in-depth and real-time process discovery, analysis, and monitoring, which help automation leaders to accelerate digital transformation initiatives as facilitators of better decisions and customer service instead of just incremental efficiency gains with the status quo.</p><p>Learn more about <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY solutions for government <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Financial Services <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Insurance <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Legal <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Process Mining <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25636/02c-reggietwigg-99x99.png"                      alt="Reggie Twigg ABBYY"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://zonlipartnershipprogram.pxf.io/c/5597632/1611407/17882" target="_top" id="1611407"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/17882-1611407"                      border="0" alt="" width="300" height="485"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1611407/17882"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p>Reginald J. Twigg</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://mushroom-supplies.sjv.io/c/5597632/1692242/18134" target="_top" id="1692242"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/18134-1692242"                      border="0" alt="" width="834" height="592"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1692242/18134"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Like-share-or-repost"><a href="#Like-share-or-repost" class="headerlink" title="Like, share or repost"></a>Like, share or repost</h3><p>Share </p><h4 id="Subscribe-for-blog-updates"><a href="#Subscribe-for-blog-updates" class="headerlink" title="Subscribe for blog updates"></a>Subscribe for blog updates</h4><p>First name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Last name</p><p>Query string</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Understanding-The-Complexities-in-Organizational-Process-Management-–-Lessons-From-the-ABBYY-Blog&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Understanding-The-Compl</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Top Strategies Für F&amp;R-Verantwortliche: Erkenntnisse Aus Dem ABBYY Gipfel Der Führenden Deutschen CFOs 201</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/top-strategies-fur-fandr-verantwortliche-erkenntnisse-aus-dem-abbyy-gipfel-der-fuhrenden-deutschen-cfos-201/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/top-strategies-fur-fandr-verantwortliche-erkenntnisse-aus-dem-abbyy-gipfel-der-fuhrenden-deutschen-cfos-201/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.611Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.611Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Top-Strategies-Fur-F-R-Verantwortliche-Erkenntnisse-Aus-Dem-ABBYY-Gipfel-Der-Fuhrenden-Deutschen-CFOs-201"><a href="#Top-Strategies-Fur-F-R-Verantwortliche-Erkenntnisse-Aus-Dem-ABBYY-Gipfel-Der-Fuhrenden-Deutschen-CFOs-201" class="headerlink" title="Top Strategies Für F&amp;R-Verantwortliche: Erkenntnisse Aus Dem ABBYY Gipfel Der Führenden Deutschen CFOs 201"></a>Top Strategies Für F&amp;R-Verantwortliche: Erkenntnisse Aus Dem ABBYY Gipfel Der Führenden Deutschen CFOs 201</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Newsroom <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="StrategieTage-Finance-2016-–-ABBYY-auf-dem-Spitzentreffen-deutscher-CFOs"><a href="#StrategieTage-Finance-2016-–-ABBYY-auf-dem-Spitzentreffen-deutscher-CFOs" class="headerlink" title="StrategieTage Finance 2016 – ABBYY auf dem Spitzentreffen deutscher CFOs"></a>StrategieTage Finance 2016 – ABBYY auf dem Spitzentreffen deutscher CFOs</h2><p>11. Februar 2016</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/branchtemplates/shutterstock_1272462163_1296-x-729.jpg?h=729&iar=0&w=1296"                                     ></p><p>ABBYY Europe, ein führender Anbieter von Technologien und Lösungen für Dokumentenerkennung, Data Capture und Linguistik, berät Finanzvorstände namhafter Unternehmen vom 17. – 18. Februar auf Schloss Bensberg zum Thema <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >automatische Kreditorenbuchhaltung <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>. Auch in diesem Jahr diskutieren deutsche CFOs auf den StrategieTagen Finance wieder die Zukunft von Finanzabteilungen. Neben den Finanzvorständen bekannter Unternehmen wie Nordzucker, ThyssenKrupp oder Universal Music sind auch prominente Gastredner aus der Politik eingeladen - unter anderem Dr. Michel Friedmann und Dr. Gregor Gysi.</p><p>„Wir freuen uns darauf, die Automatisierung der Prozesse in und um die Kreditorenbuchhaltung mit führenden Vertretern aus Politik und Wirtschaft zu diskutieren“, sagt Markus Pichler, Director Business Unit Solutions der ABBYY Europe. „Dass sich Lösungen zum Rechnungseingang lohnen, zeigen Projekte wie das <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Rechnungseingangsprojekt der Rhenus Assets &amp; Services <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.“ </p><p>ABBYY präsentiert auf den StrategieTagen Finance Lösungen für die automatische Rechnungseingangsverarbeitung. Damit können Unternehmen die Kosten in der Kreditorenbuchhaltung auf ein Minimum reduzieren – und ihre Rechnungsabwicklung bis hin zur Dunkelbuchung automatisieren. Durch die Ablösung von manuellen Arbeitsschritten entstehen im Prozess weniger Fehler. Dank modernen Geschäftsmonitorings können Unternehmen jederzeit den aktuellen Verarbeitungsstatus abrufen. Volle Transparenz ist somit immer gegeben.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY FlexiCapture for Invoices <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> eine betriebsbereite Lösung für die automatisierte Rechnungserfassung im Kreditorenbuchhaltungsprozess. Die Lösung basiert auf der Enterprise Capture Plattform <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY FlexiCapture <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> und bietet essenzielle Funktionalitäten für die automatisierte Rechnungsverarbeitung in einer Fertiglösung, die dennoch flexibel an die jeweiligen Bedürfnisse angepasst werden kann. Die Lösung ist der Schlüssel zu einer effizienten, kostengünstigen und transparenten Rechnungsverarbeitung, bis hin zur Automatisierung der Kreditorenbuchhaltung. Zudem lässt sich die Lösung auch auf die Erfassung und Verarbeitung anderer Dokumententypen im Unternehmen, wie beispielsweise Formulare in der Kundenkommunikation, Personalakten und Bestellungen, oder zum digitalen Posteingang erweitern und bietet somit eine maximale Investitionssicherheit.</p><h4 id="ABBYY-Europe-GmbH"><a href="#ABBYY-Europe-GmbH" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY Europe GmbH"></a>ABBYY Europe GmbH</h4><p>ABBYY Europe ist ein Mitglied der ABBYY Gruppe und verantwortet Vertrieb und Marketing in Westeuropa. ABBYY ist ein führender Anbieter von Technologien für Dokumentenerkennung, Data Capture und Linguistik. Zum Produktportfolio gehören ABBYY FineReader Applikationen für OCR (Optical Character Recognition), ABBYY FlexiCapture Produktreihe für Data Capture, sowie Software Development Kits für Entwickler. ABBYY bietet Professional Services, um Kunden bei der Implementierung von Business Lösungen auf Basis der ABBYY Produkte zu unterstützen. Weltweit nutzen Unternehmen mit einem hohen Aufkommen an Papierdokumenten ABBYY Software zur Automatisierung zeit- und arbeitsintensiver Verarbeitungsaufgaben und zur effizienteren Gestaltung von Businessprozessen. Staatliche Institutionen setzen ABBYY-Produkte für großvolumige Projekte ein, darunter die Australische Steuerbehörde, die Litauische Steueraufsichtsbehörde, das Russische Bildungsministerium, das Ukrainische Bildungsministerium, die Regierung des Montgomery County in den Vereinigten Staaten und die Regierung von Kanada. Zu den Lizenznehmern der Erkennungs-Technologien von ABBYY zählen: BancTec, Canon, EMC&#x2F;Captiva, Hewlett-Packard, KnowledgeLake, Microsoft, NewSoft, Notable Solutions, Samsung Electronics, u.v.m. ABBYY-Applikationen werden weltweit zusammen mit Geräten führender Hersteller ausgeliefert, darunter Epson, Fujitsu, Fuji Xerox, Microtek, Panasonic, PFU, Plustek, Ricoh, Toshiba, und Xerox. ABBYY ist ein global tätiges Unternehmen mit regionalen Niederlassungen in Deutschland, Großbritannien, Frankreich, Spanien, den USA, Kanada, Ukraine, Zypern, Australien, Japan und Taiwan. Weitere Informationen über ABBYY finden sich im Web unter <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><em>ABBYY, das ABBYY Logo, ADRT, FineReader, FlexiCapture und FlexiLayout sind entweder registrierte Warenzeichen oder Warenzeichen von ABBYY Software Ltd. Alle anderen Warenzeichen sind Eigentum ihrer jeweiligen Inhaber.</em></p><h4 id="Weitere-Informationen"><a href="#Weitere-Informationen" class="headerlink" title="Weitere Informationen"></a>Weitere Informationen</h4><p>ABBYY Europe GmbH<br>Christian Schwarzmann<br>Elsenheimerstraße 49<br>D - 80687 München<br>Tel.: +49 89 69 33 33 0<br>Fax: +49 89 69 33 33 300<br>E-Mail: press_<a class="link"   href="mailto:&#101;&#x75;&#x40;&#x61;&#98;&#98;&#121;&#121;&#x2e;&#99;&#x6f;&#109;" >&#101;&#x75;&#x40;&#x61;&#98;&#98;&#121;&#121;&#x2e;&#99;&#x6f;&#109; <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a><br>Web: <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >www.abbyy.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Pressekontakt</p><p>LEWIS PR<br>Matthias Gröschel<br>Karlstr. 64<br>D - 80335 München<br>Tel.: +49 89 17 30 19 22<br>E-Mail: <a class="link"   href="mailto:&#x61;&#x62;&#x62;&#x79;&#x79;&#103;&#x65;&#114;&#109;&#97;&#x6e;&#x79;&#x40;&#116;&#101;&#97;&#x6d;&#108;&#101;&#x77;&#105;&#x73;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#x6d;" >&#x61;&#x62;&#x62;&#x79;&#x79;&#103;&#x65;&#114;&#109;&#97;&#x6e;&#x79;&#x40;&#116;&#101;&#97;&#x6d;&#108;&#101;&#x77;&#105;&#x73;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#x6d; <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Vernetzen Sie sich mit uns</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=2201613&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.macdvdripperpro.com/images/devices-3.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end -->]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Top-Strategies-Fur-F-R-Verantwortliche-Erkenntnisse-Aus-Dem-ABBYY-Gipfel-Der-Fuhrenden-Deutschen-CFOs-201&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Top-Strategies-</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The Role of Artificial Intelligence &amp; ML in Streamlining KYC Processes for Financial Services.</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/the-role-of-artificial-intelligence-and-ml-in-streamlining-kyc-processes-for-financial-services/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/the-role-of-artificial-intelligence-and-ml-in-streamlining-kyc-processes-for-financial-services/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.605Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.605Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="The-Role-of-Artificial-Intelligence-ML-in-Streamlining-KYC-Processes-for-Financial-Services"><a href="#The-Role-of-Artificial-Intelligence-ML-in-Streamlining-KYC-Processes-for-Financial-Services" class="headerlink" title="The Role of Artificial Intelligence &amp; ML in Streamlining KYC Processes for Financial Services."></a>The Role of Artificial Intelligence &amp; ML in Streamlining KYC Processes for Financial Services.</h2><p>eBook</p><h2 id="Comment-l’IA-et-le-ML-aident-les-banques-a-garder-une-longueur-d’avance-sur-les-cybercriminels"><a href="#Comment-l’IA-et-le-ML-aident-les-banques-a-garder-une-longueur-d’avance-sur-les-cybercriminels" class="headerlink" title="Comment l’IA et le ML aident les banques à garder une longueur d’avance sur les cybercriminels"></a>Comment l’IA et le ML aident les banques à garder une longueur d’avance sur les cybercriminels</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/32234/01c-banking-on-intelligence-fr-360x232.jpg"                      alt="eBook - Comment l’IA et le ML aident les banques à garder une longueur d’avance sur les cybercriminels | ABBYY"                ></p><p>La banque est le secteur d’activité le plus coûteux en matière de cyberattaques — plus de 18,3 millions de dollars par an et par entreprise. Bien que se conformer aux règles KYC et AML puisse être efficace pour prévenir fraudes et vols, les banques doivent rester vigilantes pour garder le rythme face aux méthodes des cybercriminels qui évoluent rapidement.</p><p>Les institutions financières s’appuient de plus en plus sur l’automatisation, les technologies mobiles et les interactions sans contact pour gagner en productivité, mais ces mesures peuvent aussi être sources de nouvelles vulnérabilités que les cybercriminels exploitent. Comment les institutions financières peuvent-elles contrecarrer avec succès le flux constant d’attaques ?</p><h3 id="Telecharger-maintenant"><a href="#Telecharger-maintenant" class="headerlink" title="Télécharger maintenant!"></a>Télécharger maintenant!</h3><p>Prévenir des crimes sophistiqués nécessite des mesures sophistiquées. La Digital Intelligence propose une nouvelle approche pour utiliser les dernières technologies d’intelligence artificielle et de machine learning afin de fournir les fonctionnalités-clés qui donneront aux banques confiance dans la protection de leurs institutions tant contre la fraude que contre les violations réglementaires.</p><p>Téléchargez cet eBook pour découvrir comment la Digital Intelligence permet aux banques de :</p><ul><li>Suivre la chaîne de responsabilité des documents</li><li>Obtenir des informations sur la façon dont les gens interagissent avec les documents</li><li>Découvrir les schémas de comportements suspects dans les processus</li></ul><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://turtlebeacheu.sjv.io/c/5597632/1996818/23722" target="_top" id="1996818"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/23722-1996818"                      border="0" alt="" width="600" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1996818/23722"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Merci-de-votre-interet-pour-ABBYY"><a href="#Merci-de-votre-interet-pour-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Merci de votre intérêt pour ABBYY."></a>Merci de votre intérêt pour ABBYY.</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://digital.abbyy.com/hubfs/content/ebook-financialservices-banking-on-intelligence-fr.pdf"  title="Lire l’eBook">Lire l’eBook <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/31652/factoids-027-77x77.svg"                      alt="Factoids 027 77X77"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4621764&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.x-mirage.com/x-mirage/img/page-home.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Vous-avez-des-questions-Contactez-ABBYY"><a href="#Vous-avez-des-questions-Contactez-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Vous avez des questions ? Contactez ABBYY"></a>Vous avez des questions ? <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contactez ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></h4><h4 id="Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form"><a href="#Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form" class="headerlink" title="Get your copy by filling in the form."></a>Get your copy by filling in the form.</h4><p>Prénom*</p><p>Nom de famille*</p><p>Courriel*</p><p>Pays*</p><p>PaysAfghanistanÎles d’ÅlandAlbanieAlgérieSamoa américainesAndorreAngolaAnguillaAntarctiqueAntigua-et-BarbudaArgentineArménieArubaAustralieAutricheAzerbaïdjanBahamasBahreïnBangladeshBarbadeBelgiqueBelizeBéninBermudesBhoutanBolivieBonaire, Saint-Eustache et SabaBosnie-HerzégovineBotswanaÎle BouvetBrésilTerritoire britannique de l’océan IndienÎles Vierges britanniquesBrunéi DarussalamBulgarieBurkina FasoBurundiCambodgeCamerounCanadaCabo VerdeÎles CaïmanesRépublique centrafricaineTchadChiliChineÎle ChristmasÎles des Cocos (Keeling)ColombieComoresCongoRépublique démocratique du CongoÎles CookCosta RicaCroatieCuraçaoChypreTchéquieCôte d’IvoireDanemarkDjiboutiDominiqueRépublique dominicaineÉquateurÉgypteEl SalvadorGuinée équatorialeÉrythréeEstonieÉthiopieÎles Falkland (Malvinas)Îles FéroéFidjiFinlandeFranceGuyane françaisePolynésie françaiseTerres australes françaisesGabonGambieGéorgieAllemagneGhanaGibraltarGrèceGroenlandGrenadeGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuerneseyGuinéeGuinée-BissauGuyanaHaïtiÎle Heard-et-Îles MacDonaldSaint-SiègeHondurasHong KongHongrieIslandeIndeIndonésieIraqIrlandeÎle de ManIsraëlITJamaïqueJaponJerseyJordanieKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiRépublique de CoréeKoweïtKyrgyzstanLaosLettonieLibanLesothoLibériaLibyeLiechtensteinLituanieLuxembourgMacaoex-République yougoslave de MacédoineMadagascarMalawiMalaisieMaldivesMaliMalteÎles MarshallMartiniqueMauritanieMauriceMayotteMexiqueMicronésieRépublique de MoldovaMonacoMongolieMonténégroMontserratMarocMozambiqueMyanmarNamibieNauruNépalPays-BasAntilles NéerlandaisesNouvelle-CalédonieNouvelle-ZélandeNicaraguaNigerNigériaNiouéÎle NorfolkÎles Mariannes du NordNorvègeOmanPakistanPalaosÉtat de PalestinePanamaPapouasie-Nouvelle-GuinéeParaguayPérouPhilippinesPitcairnPolognePortugalPorto RicoQatarRoumanieRwandaRéunionSainte-HélèneSaint-Kitts-et-NevisSainte-LucieSaint-Pierre-et-MiquelonSaint-Vincent-et-les GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (partie française)SamoaSaint-MarinSao Tomé-et-PrincipeArabie saouditeSénégalSerbieSeychellesSierra LeoneSingapourSaint-Martin (partie néerlandaise)SlovaquieSlovénieÎles SalomonAfrique du SudGéorgie du Sud-et-les Îles Sandwich du SudSoudan du SudEspagneSri LankaSurinameÎles Svalbard-et-Jan MayenSwazilandSuèdeSuisseTaïwanTadjikistanTanzanieThaïlandeTimor-LesteTogoTokélaouTongaTrinité-et-TobagoTunisieTurquieÎles Turques-et-CaïquesTuvaluOugandaUkraineÉmirats arabes unisRoyaume-UniÉtats-Unis d’AmériqueUruguayÎles mineures éloignées des États-UnisOuzbékistanVanuatuVenezuelaViet NamÎles Vierges américainesÎles Wallis-et-FutunaSahara occidentalZambieZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>J’ai lu et j’accepte la <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Politique relative à la vie privée <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> et la <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Politique relative aux cookies <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.*</p></li><li><p>J’accepte de recevoir des e-mails d’ABBYY Solutions Ltd., des actualités concernant leur produits et technologies, des invitations à des événements et webinaires, des informations sur les livres blancs et tout contenu lié aux produits et services ABBYY Solutions Ltd..</p></li></ul><p>J’ai été informé que je peux retirer mon consentement à tout moment en cliquant sur le lien de désabonnement se trouvant dans tout email reçu d’ABBYY Solutions Ltd. ou en utilisant le <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >formulaire Droits d’accès aux données personnelles d’ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Salutation</p><p>Academic Title</p><p>Query string</p><p>Posez une question ou décrivez votre demande </p><p>Business Scenario Temp</p><p>City</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;The-Role-of-Artificial-Intelligence-ML-in-Streamlining-KYC-Processes-for-Financial-Services&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#The-Role-of-Artificial-Intell</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Senior Recruitment Expert Paula Dam at ABBYY: Leading the Way in Talent Acquisition Strategies</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/senior-recruitment-expert-paula-dam-at-abbyy-leading-the-way-in-talent-acquisition-strategies/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/senior-recruitment-expert-paula-dam-at-abbyy-leading-the-way-in-talent-acquisition-strategies/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.599Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.599Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Senior-Recruitment-Expert-Paula-Dam-at-ABBYY-Leading-the-Way-in-Talent-Acquisition-Strategies"><a href="#Senior-Recruitment-Expert-Paula-Dam-at-ABBYY-Leading-the-Way-in-Talent-Acquisition-Strategies" class="headerlink" title="Senior Recruitment Expert Paula Dam at ABBYY: Leading the Way in Talent Acquisition Strategies"></a>Senior Recruitment Expert Paula Dam at ABBYY: Leading the Way in Talent Acquisition Strategies</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to ABBYY Blog <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h1 id="ABBYY-Spotlight-Paula-Dam-Dieu-Phuong-Senior-Talent-Acquisition-Partner"><a href="#ABBYY-Spotlight-Paula-Dam-Dieu-Phuong-Senior-Talent-Acquisition-Partner" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY Spotlight: Paula Đàm Diệu Phương, Senior Talent Acquisition Partner"></a>ABBYY Spotlight: Paula Đàm Diệu Phương, Senior Talent Acquisition Partner</h1><p>May 12, 2023</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/37761/paula-%C4%91%C3%A0m-di%E1%BB%87u-ph%C6%B0%C6%A1ng.png"                                     > </p><p>Flexible working was a deal clincher for Paula Dam when she joined ABBYY—and now we know why! The Senior Talent Acquisition Partner certainly has an active personal life—including running, cycling, canoeing, volunteering, and travelling, which only comes after her daily ritual of meditation.</p><p>And flexibility and remote working are not the only perks that attracted Paula to ABBYY. She says our team spirit and endless support from colleagues makes her feel appreciated and motivated. Here’s what else she had to say about life at ABBYY…</p><p><strong><a class="link"   href="https://www.instagram.com/abbyyglobal/"  title="Instagram">Follow us on Instagram and get to know the people at ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></strong></p><h3 id="What-is-it-that-you-do-at-ABBYY-and-what-is-your-favorite-thing-about-it"><a href="#What-is-it-that-you-do-at-ABBYY-and-what-is-your-favorite-thing-about-it" class="headerlink" title="What is it that you do at ABBYY and what is your favorite thing about it?"></a>What is it that you do at ABBYY and what is your favorite thing about it?</h3><p>I am the Senior Talent Acquisition Partner at ABBYY’s regional Asia-Pacific (APAC) headquarters in Singapore. We are the ambassadors of ABBYY when it comes to hiring. I work hand in hand with hiring managers on identifying and recruiting people from across the Asia-Pacific and Japan (APJ) region and I am usually the first person to interact and engage with those who will potentially become ABBYY colleagues!</p><p>What I like about my job is engaging with different candidates across the region, building a network and relationship with external stakeholders as well as the internal stakeholders, and more importantly, finding the right talent for our teams!</p><h3 id="What-does-a-typical-day-look-like-for-you-at-ABBYY"><a href="#What-does-a-typical-day-look-like-for-you-at-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="What does a typical day look like for you at ABBYY?"></a>What does a typical day look like for you at ABBYY?</h3><p>The most important thing I do to start my day is to practice Vipassana meditation for 30-45 minutes which helps me to have a strong and healthy mind throughout the day.</p><p>I then spend 10 mins writing a daily task list and prioritizing the tasks before kick-starting my workday. Generally, in the morning, I do talent searching, head hunting, job posting, shortlisting applicants, and arranging the first interviews with candidates. Late morning and in the afternoon, it’s time for me to interview shortlisted applicants, send their details to respective hiring managers, arrange interviews between hiring managers and applicants, follow up on their feedback and complete other tasks.</p><p>In the evening, I have a catch-up meeting with my manager, Talent Acquisition (TA) colleagues, the People team, hiring managers, and others. Sometimes I join my colleagues in Singapore for lunch or go running and cycling in the late afternoon to take a break from work.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/37164/meet-paula-dam-1.png?width=750&height=570"                                     ></p><h3 id="What-was-your-previous-experience-before-ABBYY"><a href="#What-was-your-previous-experience-before-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="What was your previous experience before ABBYY?"></a>What was your previous experience before ABBYY?</h3><p>I have more than 10 years of experience in recruitment, working on the agency side as a headhunter before moving to in-house recruitment in 2021. In the last six years, my recruitment focus has been in the technology space, taking care of the recruitment for both technical and commercial roles in tech across the APAC region.</p><p>Prior to joining ABBYY, I worked for Everbridge, a Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) based company specializing in critical event management and mass warning alerts. There, I was the recruiter for all hiring across the APJ region.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=195080&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.blumentals.net/scrwonder/images/screensaver-software.png"                      border="0"                >With Screensaver Wonder you can easily make a screensaver from your own pictures and video files. Create screensavers for your own computer or create standalone, self-installing screensavers for easy sharing with your friends. Together with its sister product Screensaver Factory, Screensaver Wonder is one of the most popular screensaver software products in the world, helping thousands of users decorate their computer screens quickly and easily.</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="What-attracted-you-to-ABBYY-what-made-you-join"><a href="#What-attracted-you-to-ABBYY-what-made-you-join" class="headerlink" title="What attracted you to ABBYY, what made you join?"></a>What attracted you to ABBYY, what made you join?</h3><p>The reason I accepted the offer from ABBYY was due to the company’s stance on flexible working. Thanks to my manager, Steve Bettini and ABBYY, I have a remote working agreement which allows me to manage my work-life balance. Another factor for joining the company was being the first TA partner in Asia. I could see my potential career growth in the future with ABBYY!</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/37165/meet-paula-dam-2.png?width=750&height=570"                                     ></p><h3 id="What-keeps-you-going-and-what-are-some-highlights-of-your-journey-with-ABBYY-so-far"><a href="#What-keeps-you-going-and-what-are-some-highlights-of-your-journey-with-ABBYY-so-far" class="headerlink" title="What keeps you going, and what are some highlights of your journey with ABBYY so far?"></a>What keeps you going, and what are some highlights of your journey with ABBYY so far?</h3><p>Besides what made me join ABBYY, I think another important factor is what’s making me stay. For me, it’s the people – my colleagues in the Singapore office, Japan, and across ABBYY worldwide.</p><p>We all work as a team, trying to help each other to achieve overall results, and taking care of each other—an internal motto is #OneABBYY. That makes me feel like I am part of a real community at ABBYY. Another important thing I appreciate is that my voice and ideas are heard, and my hard work is recognized.</p><p>I am blessed to be part of ABBYY and surrounded by great leaders in the region, such as Derek Poh, Mariko Maeda, Michael Lazarri, Steven Cronin, Liubomyr Poliarush, Uliana Kis, Kateryna Shykova, Alina Dernova, Natalia Volodko, Sundarraj Subramani, Dimitri Nefedov, Laura dell’Acqua, and other hiring managers that I have the opportunity to support and work with. Also, I am lucky enough to be under the guidance of Steve Bettini and Weronika Niemczyk, both of whom are great leaders!</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Learn from senior executives and ABBYY customers on how to successfully adapt to contemporary challenges using innovative technologies | ABBYY’s The Intelligent Enterprise <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/37166/meet-paula-dam-3.png?width=750&height=570"                                     ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://estore.macxdvd.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4526659&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.macxdvd.com/affiliate/new-banner/vcp-500x500.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4726960&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/5f4f7141b65a730b4efb0e0d51f63e94/products/forexrobotronbox.gif"                      border="0"                >Forex Robotron Basic Package</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Your-top-advice-to-someone-joining-ABBYY-and-for-someone-joining-ABBYY-in-a-similar-role"><a href="#Your-top-advice-to-someone-joining-ABBYY-and-for-someone-joining-ABBYY-in-a-similar-role" class="headerlink" title="Your top advice to someone joining ABBYY, and for someone joining ABBYY in a similar role?"></a>Your top advice to someone joining ABBYY, and for someone joining ABBYY in a similar role?</h3><p>If you are someone who likes challenges, wants to make a change, and create something new, ABBYY will give you that opportunity. It’s a place where you will enjoy taking the initiative and figuring out new ways to work as if this is your own business. You are part of ABBYY and ABBYY is part of you.</p><p>ABBYY has more than 30 years in the business yet, in many ways, it maintains a startup mentality. Your experience and ideas will be somehow utilized, and you’ll be a great contribution to our organization. It’s an adult working environment. You just need some principal guidelines, and then you can ride the boat as a ‘captain’ in your field.</p><h3 id="We-know-that-you-are-living-an-active-lifestyle-Tell-us-more-about-it-how-do-you-spend-your-free-time"><a href="#We-know-that-you-are-living-an-active-lifestyle-Tell-us-more-about-it-how-do-you-spend-your-free-time" class="headerlink" title="We know that you are living an active lifestyle. Tell us more about it, how do you spend your free time?"></a>We know that you are living an active lifestyle. Tell us more about it, how do you spend your free time?</h3><p>I am committed to taking care of myself both physically and mentally. Physically, I try to explore different sports and enjoy running and cycling. The longest distance I ever ran was a full marathon, but I regularly jog between 5-10 kilometer (km). I sometimes join my friends biking around Singapore and on average we cycle 40-70 km. I also practice outrigger canoeing (OC) at Sentosa Island during the weekend and early in the morning before starting work (5am to 6.30pm is our weekday training session).</p><p>Other than sports, I do several volunteering activities. I am a regular volunteer with Waterways Watch Society – a Singaporean non-profit environmental organization. Our work is to foster appreciation and promote conservation of our environment. You might spot me cleaning the litter along Kallang River, Boat Quay and the Merlion area.</p><p>Besides my environmental and sustainability activities, I am also a regular volunteer with Team Nila, a national movement that promotes the culture of giving, citizenship, and social cohesion through sport. This year I am volunteering as team lead taking care of the Canoe Polo competition, which is part of the 2023 Singapore National Day, a sort of festival of sports.</p><p>For my mental health, I practice Vipassana mediation every morning. Travelling is also a big part of my life. I travel to learn, connect, and experience new things.</p><h3 id="If-you-could-have-one-wish-come-true-what-would-it-be-and-why"><a href="#If-you-could-have-one-wish-come-true-what-would-it-be-and-why" class="headerlink" title="If you could have one wish come true, what would it be and why?"></a>If you could have one wish come true, what would it be and why?</h3><p>I don’t really believe in wishes coming true or hypotheses. If you want something, work and find a way to achieve it instead of wishing. If we face challenges and tough times in our lives, we may be able to handle them with our own great courage and attitude.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/37167/meet-paula-dam-4.png?width=750&height=570"                                     ></p><h3 id="What-is-your-definition-of-work-life-balance"><a href="#What-is-your-definition-of-work-life-balance" class="headerlink" title="What is your definition of work-life balance?"></a>What is your definition of work-life balance?</h3><p>It’s when I am excited about starting work in the morning, continue to enjoy it during the day and at the same time have my personal life fulfilled. It’s when I am going to sleep happily knowing that I have had a fulfilled and meaningful, yet challenging day!</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://homestyler.sjv.io/c/5597632/2044747/22993" target="_top" id="2044747"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/22993-2044747"                      border="0" alt="" width="300" height="250"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/2044747/22993"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Lastly-could-you-recommend-us-a-book-movie-series-or-activity-you-have-recently-discovered-or-are-enjoying-at-the-moment-What’s-so-great-about-it"><a href="#Lastly-could-you-recommend-us-a-book-movie-series-or-activity-you-have-recently-discovered-or-are-enjoying-at-the-moment-What’s-so-great-about-it" class="headerlink" title="Lastly, could you recommend us a book&#x2F;movie&#x2F;series&#x2F; or activity you have recently discovered or are enjoying at the moment? What’s so great about it?"></a>Lastly, could you recommend us a book&#x2F;movie&#x2F;series&#x2F; or activity you have recently discovered or are enjoying at the moment? What’s so great about it?</h3><p>Meditation: practice Vipassana Mediation! I went to the 10 days Vipassana Mediation taught by S.N Goenka in the tradition of Sayagyi last Christmas in Bali. It was a life-changing experience and I have had so much benefit from a mental health perspective.</p><p>It’s the art of how to live our lives peacefully. For those curious, here is the <a class="link"   href="https://www.dhamma.org/en-US/index" >link for more information <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>There are two books I recommend:</p><ul><li><em>The Power of Now</em> by Eckhart Tolle</li><li><em>The Art of Communicating</em> by Thich Nhat Hanh</li></ul><p>Both books can be easily found on the internet and if you prefer audiobooks, they are available for free on YouTube!</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://estore.winxdvd.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4612444&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.winxdvd.com/affiliate/new-banner/pt-728x90.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Interested-in-joining-the-ABBYY-team-Please-check-the-vacancies-below-and-apply"><a href="#Interested-in-joining-the-ABBYY-team-Please-check-the-vacancies-below-and-apply" class="headerlink" title="Interested in joining the ABBYY team? Please check the vacancies below and apply!"></a>Interested in joining the ABBYY team? Please check the vacancies below and apply!</h3><p><a class="link"   href="https://boards.eu.greenhouse.io/abbyy?itm_source=corpblog" >See all open positions <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Meet Our Team <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://otszone.ots7.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4713322&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://green.ots7.com/screenshots/OtsAV/OtsAVRadio1.90-300x188.jpg"                      border="0"                >OtsAV Radio Webcaster</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Like-share-or-repost"><a href="#Like-share-or-repost" class="headerlink" title="Like, share or repost"></a>Like, share or repost</h3><p>Share </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://shop.emeditor.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4610657&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.emeditor.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/emeditor_chat_ai.png"                      border="0"                ><br>EmEditor is a fast, lightweight, yet extensible, easy-to-use text editor, code editor, CSV editor, and large file viewer for Windows. Both native 64-bit and 32-bit builds are available, and moreover, the 64-bit includes separate builds for SSE2 (128-bit), AVX-2 (256-bit), and AVX-512 (512-bit) instruction sets. New versions support AI-assisted writing.</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Related-posts"><a href="#Related-posts" class="headerlink" title="Related posts"></a>Related posts</h3><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/37760/nina-walker.png"                                     > </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Spotlight: Nina Walker, Head of Customer Experience <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static5.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/37764/viacheslav-prodan.png"                                     > </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=2201613&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.macdvdripperpro.com/images/devices-3.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p><a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/blog/meet-viacheslav-prodan/" >ABBYY Spotlight: Viacheslav Prodan, Director Customer Excellence (CEx) Systems, Processes, and Automations <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h4 id="Subscribe-for-blog-updates"><a href="#Subscribe-for-blog-updates" class="headerlink" title="Subscribe for blog updates"></a>Subscribe for blog updates</h4><p>First name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Last name</p><p>Query string</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Senior-Recruitment-Expert-Paula-Dam-at-ABBYY-Leading-the-Way-in-Talent-Acquisition-Strategies&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Senior-Recruitment-Expert-P</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Revolutionizing School Portraits with Streamlined, Automatic Document Upload Technology for Better Results</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/revolutionizing-school-portraits-with-streamlined-automatic-document-upload-technology-for-better-results/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/revolutionizing-school-portraits-with-streamlined-automatic-document-upload-technology-for-better-results/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.584Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.584Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Revolutionizing-School-Portraits-with-Streamlined-Automatic-Document-Upload-Technology-for-Better-Results"><a href="#Revolutionizing-School-Portraits-with-Streamlined-Automatic-Document-Upload-Technology-for-Better-Results" class="headerlink" title="Revolutionizing School Portraits with Streamlined, Automatic Document Upload Technology for Better Results"></a>Revolutionizing School Portraits with Streamlined, Automatic Document Upload Technology for Better Results</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Customer stories <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Other | Forms Processing</p><h2 id="School-photography-studio-raises-efficiency-with-automated-form-capture"><a href="#School-photography-studio-raises-efficiency-with-automated-form-capture" class="headerlink" title="School photography studio raises efficiency with automated form capture"></a>School photography studio raises efficiency with automated form capture</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/logos-white/abbyy.png?h=40&iar=0&w=120"                      alt="pathner logo"                ></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Customer stories <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="School-photography-studio-raises-efficiency-with-automated-form-capture-1"><a href="#School-photography-studio-raises-efficiency-with-automated-form-capture-1" class="headerlink" title="School photography studio raises efficiency with automated form capture"></a>School photography studio raises efficiency with automated form capture</h2><p>Other | Forms Processing </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/15571/20-rolland-studios-1.png"                                     > </p><h4 id="Customer-Overview"><a href="#Customer-Overview" class="headerlink" title="Customer Overview"></a>Customer Overview</h4><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static3.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/15408/rolland-studios-logo-155.jpg"                      alt="Rolland Studios"                > </p><table><thead><tr><th>Name</th><th>Rolland Studios</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Headquarters</td><td>Raytown Missouri, USA</td></tr><tr><td>Industry</td><td>School photography</td></tr><tr><td>Web</td><td><a class="link"   href="https://www.rollandstudiosinc.com/" >www.rollandstudiosinc.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></td></tr></tbody></table><h4 id="Partner-Overview"><a href="#Partner-Overview" class="headerlink" title="Partner Overview"></a>Partner Overview</h4><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/15269/wisetrend_logo.jpg"                      alt="WiseTREND"                > </p><table><thead><tr><th>Name</th><th>WiseTREND</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Headquarters</td><td>Fremont, CA, USA</td></tr><tr><td>Industry</td><td>OCR and data capture</td></tr><tr><td>Web</td><td><a class="link"   href="https://www.wisetrend.com/" >www.wisetrend.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></td></tr></tbody></table><h6 id="CHALLENGE"><a href="#CHALLENGE" class="headerlink" title="CHALLENGE"></a>CHALLENGE</h6><p>Enable Rolland Studios to replace slow and error-prone manual data entry with automated form processing</p><h6 id="SOLUTION"><a href="#SOLUTION" class="headerlink" title="SOLUTION"></a>SOLUTION</h6><p>ABBYY FlexiCapture </p><h6 id="RESULTS"><a href="#RESULTS" class="headerlink" title="RESULTS"></a>RESULTS</h6><p>Rolland Studios has leveraged ABBYY FlexiCapture to automate the processing of forms – greatly lowering the time it takes to process them and virtually eliminating errors.</p><p>Rolland Studios offers a complete range of photographic services for K-12 schools. During its busiest period, Rolland has to photograph 60,000 students in just ten weeks – and deliver customized print packages within two weeks of each shoot. But manual entry of order and pricing data from forms into the company database was slow and error-prone – costing Rolland time and money until <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY FlexiCapture® <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> provided a solution that automated the process.</p><p> “Data entry used to be a major part of our processes. ABBYY FlexiCapture has completely eliminated it. This really is a “Wow!”</p><p> Steve J. Mullally, President at Rolland Studios</p><h4 id="Losing-productivity-to-human-error"><a href="#Losing-productivity-to-human-error" class="headerlink" title="Losing productivity to human error"></a>Losing productivity to human error</h4><p>School photography has come a long way since Rolland Studios first opened its doors. Behind every photograph there is now a network of processes dependent on fast and accurate data input. From the time a student’s picture is taken to when their package of prints is delivered, information including name, print sizes, special services and payment details has to be input into a database, correlated and matched to their digital photo. </p><p>And according to Rolland’s President Steve Mullally, timeframes are short and the need for efficiency huge: “Between mid-August and November 1st we photograph 60,000 kids and send out a customized package for each one. Plus, we commit to a very fast turnaround on our packages – two weeks from photo shoot to delivery. Manually entering the information for each of those data points was impacting our efficiency and resources.”</p><p>Rolland had evolved a system where a barcode was assigned to each digital photo taken onsite, and then associated with a form specifying package options – making it easy to match a JPEG with order information within the database. But as Mr. Mullally describes, “We had to scan in each one of those forms’ codes with a handheld barcode scanner and then manually enter each form’s information into the system. If we made a mistake, for example if the dollar amount didn’t match what we collected at the shoot, we had redo it and that cost us 15 minutes per package – six times the time we are running at today.” </p><h4 id="Have-a-task-Let’s-find-a-solution"><a href="#Have-a-task-Let’s-find-a-solution" class="headerlink" title="Have a task? Let’s find a solution"></a>Have a task? Let’s find a solution</h4><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contact Us <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h4 id="Pursuing-a-solution-to-inefficient-manual-input…"><a href="#Pursuing-a-solution-to-inefficient-manual-input…" class="headerlink" title="Pursuing a solution to inefficient manual input…"></a>Pursuing a solution to inefficient manual input…</h4><p>“We knew,” says Mullally, “that there had to be a better way. After the actual photography, data entry was the most labor-intensive part of our process and the most inefficient. So we began looking for methods of automating input of the information on our forms.”</p><p>Much research and a strong recommendation from Rolland’s IT consultant led Mullally and his team to identify ABBYY FlexiCapture as their best option: “ABBYY really was the Cadillac choice,” says Mullally. “And thanks to a reference from Toshiba Business Solutions we found the right partner for implementation: Ilya Evdokimov from WiseTREND. That’s when things really took off.”</p><h4 id="Reclaiming-time-and-efficiency-with-ABBYY-FlexiCapture"><a href="#Reclaiming-time-and-efficiency-with-ABBYY-FlexiCapture" class="headerlink" title="Reclaiming time and efficiency with ABBYY FlexiCapture"></a>Reclaiming time and efficiency with ABBYY FlexiCapture</h4><p>Working with Mullally, Evdokimov formulated the criteria for automating and validating form capture using FlexiCapture. “Mr. Mullally envisioned this as a highly automated process,” says Evdokimov, “and in our conversations I could see how the software’s flexibility would eliminate most manual processes.”</p><p>In line with expectations, Evdokimov began configuring FlexiCapture, implementing a series of checks and crosschecks for automatic form validation and correction. “If there were values out of range,” explains Evdokimov, “or multiple checkmarks were checked where only one checkmark was needed, FlexiCapture was set to automatically perform corrections, or inform operators – relieving them from the multiple tasks previously required to correct a form. It was also set up to perform database checks and import values from external resources – enabling the amount of data on the form itself to be minimized, thus requiring less capture work, while still providing operators all the necessary data points.”</p><p>“Just being alerted to mismatches between the dollar amount and the form package is an enormous timesaver,” says Mullally. “Having the system flag us is very helpful. If you’re talking 15 minutes to correct a mistake, catching them beforehand saves huge amounts of time.”</p><p>“Our clients are not in the business of data entry,” says Evdokimov, “but they still need to do data entry as part of their business. So our goal is to eliminate or at least minimize it, empowering our clients to focus on their core expertise.” </p><h4 id="Results"><a href="#Results" class="headerlink" title="Results"></a>Results</h4><p>According to Mullally, implementing FlexiCapture was fast and straightforward: “From the time we gave Ilya the go-ahead it took one week, start to finish. The solution was installed on a dual quad-core Windows-based Dell PC, and the process was no more complicated than installing Word or any other off-the-shelf Windows product. Ilya then did a walk-through over the phone and we were up and running – we haven’t required any support since.”</p><p> “Before ABBYY we had a person doing data entry full time and it took three to four hours to manually process the forms for each school. Now it’s down to between 30 to 40 minutes, only requires one operator on a part-time basis and the accuracy is 100%. Overall it takes 75% less time to get everything done. This really is a “Wow.”</p><p> Steve J. Mullally, President at Rolland Studios</p><p>“If you’re in this business,” says Mullally, “you’d be silly not to use this. I highly recommend it. Manual data entry can be a huge time consuming part of the job and this eliminates it. Plus,” he adds, “Toshiba Business Solutions and WiseTREND were great and did a tremendous job. It’s been everything abusiness relationship should be.”</p><p><a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static2.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/21380/4-flexicapture.jpg"                      alt="4-flexicapture"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY FlexiCapture <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >read more <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/14365/15-education.jpg"                      alt="15-education"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Education <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >read more <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a href="https://static3.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/1234/f%D1%81%5Frolland%5Fstudios%5Feducation-and-science%5F2014.pdf" title="PDF version"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/15572/20-rolland-studios-2.png"                      alt="(20) Rolland Studios-2"                ></a> <a class="link"   href="https://static3.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/1234/f%D1%81%5Frolland%5Fstudios%5Feducation-and-science%5F2014.pdf"  title="PDF version">PDF version <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://static3.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/1234/f%D1%81%5Frolland%5Fstudios%5Feducation-and-science%5F2014.pdf"  title="PDF version">read more <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h6 id="Like-share-or-repost"><a href="#Like-share-or-repost" class="headerlink" title="Like, share or repost"></a>Like, share or repost</h6><p>Share  True ?  : “” </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >More about ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Find your ABBYY office <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://appsumo.8odi.net/c/5597632/2087394/7443" target="_top" id="2087394"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/7443-2087394"                      border="0" alt="" width="1200" height="600"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://appsumo.8odi.net/i/5597632/2087394/7443"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Ready-to-talk-to-an-expert"><a href="#Ready-to-talk-to-an-expert" class="headerlink" title="Ready to talk to an expert?"></a>Ready to talk to an expert?</h3><p>We’d love to help you along your automation journey.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contact us <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Revolutionizing-School-Portraits-with-Streamlined-Automatic-Document-Upload-Technology-for-Better-Results&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Revolutionizing</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Revolutionize Your Paperwork: Unveiling the Power of ABBYY Vantage Version 2.1</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/revolutionize-your-paperwork-unveiling-the-power-of-abbyy-vantage-version-21/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/revolutionize-your-paperwork-unveiling-the-power-of-abbyy-vantage-version-21/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.572Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.572Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Revolutionize-Your-Paperwork-Unveiling-the-Power-of-ABBYY-Vantage-Version-2-1"><a href="#Revolutionize-Your-Paperwork-Unveiling-the-Power-of-ABBYY-Vantage-Version-2-1" class="headerlink" title="Revolutionize Your Paperwork: Unveiling the Power of ABBYY Vantage Version 2.1"></a>Revolutionize Your Paperwork: Unveiling the Power of ABBYY Vantage Version 2.1</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to ABBYY Blog <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h1 id="Leveling-Up-Document-Processing-with-ABBYY-Vantage-v2-1"><a href="#Leveling-Up-Document-Processing-with-ABBYY-Vantage-v2-1" class="headerlink" title="Leveling Up Document Processing with ABBYY Vantage v2.1"></a>Leveling Up Document Processing with ABBYY Vantage v2.1</h1><h6 id="Bill-Galusha"><a href="#Bill-Galusha" class="headerlink" title="Bill Galusha"></a>Bill Galusha</h6><p>December 13, 2021</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/34966/14194-main.jpg"                                     > </p><h2 id="Features-and-new-innovative-technology-to-make-business-user-developer-and-partner-experiences-simpler-faster-and-more-valuable"><a href="#Features-and-new-innovative-technology-to-make-business-user-developer-and-partner-experiences-simpler-faster-and-more-valuable" class="headerlink" title="Features and new innovative technology to make business user, developer, and partner experiences simpler, faster, and more valuable"></a>Features and new innovative technology to make business user, developer, and partner experiences simpler, faster, and more valuable</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back in August <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, ABBYY Vantage 2.0 took the market by storm by offering the first ever low-code &#x2F; no-code design approach to intelligent document processing. Currently, over 400 businesses and partners have signed on for a trial. In addition to Vantage being a new <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >cloud-native platform <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, we introduced the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Marketplace <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and several pre-trained document skills (models) that brought instant value to any enterprise looking to automate processes involving invoices, purchase orders, remittance advice, tax forms, and many other documents.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Learn more about ABBYY’s low-code &#x2F; no-code solution for Intelligent Document Processing. <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Now with the release of <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Vantage v2.1 <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, we are introducing more than 50 new enhancements touching Vantage in all areas. Today’s announcement represents a giant leap forward in solving complex document processing challenges using best-in-class no-code intelligent document processing powered by ABBYY’s leading artificial intelligence (AI) technology.</p><p>Let me walk you through some of the key highlights.</p><h2 id="Putting-the-power-of-AI-into-the-hands-of-all-end-users-developers-and-partners"><a href="#Putting-the-power-of-AI-into-the-hands-of-all-end-users-developers-and-partners" class="headerlink" title="Putting the power of AI into the hands of all end users, developers, and partners"></a>Putting the power of AI into the hands of all end users, developers, and partners</h2><p>The <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Vantage v2.1 release <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> includes a variety of enhancements focused on making it easier for developers to build, for end users to find and use simple automations, and for partners to grow revenue streams while serving their clients better.</p><p><strong>For citizen developers</strong>, we added several new point-and-click activities into the process skill designer for importing emails and attachments, and to handle transactions involving several different documents as part of one transaction. There’s also a new activity that can be easily configured to split documents by classification, combine all pages into one document file, or classify each document as its own type. These new features meet the needs of several processes that call for processing documents together, such as onboarding a customer, processing a loan, or handling multi-invoice financial transactions.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/34964/14194-2.jpg"                      alt="How to train a process skill in ABBYY Vantage"                ></p><p>Training a skill and then reviewing the results got a lot easier with a redesign of the results screen. Results now show more granular field accuracy information after training, including recognition issues (low confidence), field located incorrectly, or field not detected. In the case of field located incorrectly, the user interface (UI) displays the reference label, prediction, and difference between the reference and prediction. It makes it much easier for training and perfecting the accuracy of a skill.</p><p><strong>For developers</strong>, we added two new activities to connect to external AI services, and for creating custom export scripts to connect directly to applications. These new activities provide the flexibility to integrate third party AI services and applications via a script to call an application or service has a REST API. The custom activity makes it easier for developers to incorporate AI into a Vantage process flow, which covers any number of services.</p><p><strong>For end users</strong>, we’ve added enhancements for reviewing tables to speed up the process where you no longer must be concerned about a table where values are not filled because the tables are not present in the document. Vantage automatically detects and only shows the table columns that are relevant to the document being reviewed. This is extremely useful when you have many variations of a document, but the table columns are not always the same for each variation.</p><p>To get started, users of Vantage can access the FREE <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >online training and certifications <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> courses.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><span id="1793213">                    <video width="1080" height="1620" style="cursor:pointer"           poster="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-clicktoplayimage/1793213.jpeg"           onclick="if(!this.playClicked){this.play();this.setAttribute('controls',true);this.playClicked=true;}">       <source src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/19135-1793213">       <img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-clicktoplayimage/1793213.jpeg"                      style="border: none; height: 100%; width: 100%; object-fit: contain"                >    </video>    <div style="width:1080px;text-align:center"><a class="link"   href="javascript:window.open(decodeURIComponent('https%3A%2F%2Ftinyland.pxf.io%2Fc%2F5597632%2F1793213%2F19135'), '_blank');void(0);" >Click here <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></div></span><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1793213/19135"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ><!-- affiliate ads end -->## New supply chain document skills<p>No release of Vantage is complete without introducing a new set of pre-trained machine learning (ML) models delivered as document skills. In Vantage v2.1 we’ve added new out-of-the-box, production-ready skills for several documents that are common in supply chain.</p><p>Those include:</p><ul><li><strong><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Commercial Invoice <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></strong> a new trained document skill automatically extracting data for vendor, consignee, invoice number and date, ship to and bill to addresses, total, INCO terms, transportation mode, line items etc.).</li><li><strong><a class="link"   href="https://marketplace.abbyy.com/root/bill-of-lading-en/?itm_source=corpblog-en" >Bill of Lading (BoL) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></strong> a new trained document skill automatically detects key fields on and extracting data for BoL number and date, PO number, shipper, carrier, consignee and bill to addresses, shipment ID and date, terms, port of entry&#x2F;exit, hazardous material etc.</li><li><strong><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Airway bill <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></strong> a new trained document skill automatically detects key fields on AWB documents and extracting data for AWB number and date, shipper, carrier, consignee, airline addresses (parsed), airport of departure, destination, line items, charges, etc.</li><li><strong><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Invoices for China <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></strong> a new trained document skill for Chinese invoice documents. It can extract information about the seller and purchaser, invoice number and date, data about the commodities, amounts, taxes, and other fields.</li></ul><p>A new set of framework skills for processing tax documents including 1098 and 1099 (DIV, G, MISC, INT, NEC, and R) are available in the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Marketplace <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> for users to try out.</p><p>What’s important to point out about the trained skills is that these document skill models can be further trained by users based on their own customer documents. The power of continuously collecting documents and data and retraining the model is built into the Vantage human-in-the-loop capabilities. Once you publish a skill(s) into production and enable online learning, every time a human operator validates exceptions or makes corrections, that information is stored and used to update the learning model. Eventually, your document processes achieve a higher degree of accuracy and straight through processing.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.textstudio.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=35633281&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"> <img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/d6eb8222c9718486bdabce8b897380f7/products/2_premium-icon.png"                      border="0"                > Take advantage of PREMIUM features.<br>Create your texts &#x2F; logos without any limitation.<br>No attribution required when downloading.<br>No advertising on the website.<br> TextStudio.com  PREMIUM - Monthly Membership</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="ABBYY-Marketplace-growing-momentum"><a href="#ABBYY-Marketplace-growing-momentum" class="headerlink" title="ABBYY Marketplace growing momentum"></a>ABBYY Marketplace growing momentum</h2><p>We first launched the marketplace in August 2021, and since then, 30 more assets have been added by ABBYY and our partners. New assets include pre-trained skills, connectors, and solutions that are simple-to-use and accelerate the deployment of IDP projects. Expect this marketplace to lead the way into the future on how enterprises will want to start every document automation project.</p><p>For ABBYY partners, the marketplace is open for your contributions. ABBYY partners like <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >oAppNet <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >WizeTREND <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >User Friendly Consulting <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Incture <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Jobes Technology, <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and several others are contributing regularly.</p><p>Technology alliance partners like <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Pipefy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Toca <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >NICE <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>, and <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cognigy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> have developed connectors to their applications as well. In the marketplace, we have added a way for registered users to comment on your assets, search for solutions that match their needs, and inquiry directly with partners about your assets.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Calling ISVs and Partners: Upskill Your Business Solutions to Intelligently Process Documents <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://twopages.pxf.io/c/5597632/1873313/18544" target="_top" id="1873313"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="//a.impactradius-go.com/display-ad/18544-1873313"                      border="0" alt="" width="1080" height="1263"                ></a><img  height="0" width="0"                      lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://imp.pxf.io/i/5597632/1873313/18544"                      style="position:absolute;visibility:hidden;" border="0"                 ></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Advancing-document-skills-training-for-the-developer"><a href="#Advancing-document-skills-training-for-the-developer" class="headerlink" title="Advancing document skills training for the developer"></a>Advancing document skills training for the developer</h2><p>In this release, we have something for every type of user, including the skilled expert who understands the fine art of machine learning, natural language processing (NLP), and named entity recognition (NER). We are pleased to introduce the new Vantage Advanced Skill Designer (available in controlled release), a point-and-click design studio that opens the door to building out the processing pipeline of a trained document skill model.</p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/34963/14194-1.jpg"                      alt="Advanced Designer ABBYY Vantage interface"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://otszone.ots7.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4713322&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://green.ots7.com/screenshots/OtsAV/OtsAVRadio1.90-300x188.jpg"                      border="0"                >OtsAV Radio Webcaster</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><p>The Advanced Skill Designer includes a set of activities for parsing address fields, training NLP for segmentation, or leveraging trained NER to extract entities like names, address, business, dates, and currency. An activity for defining data extraction for edge case document variations that machine learning is unable to pick up at a high degree of accuracy is also possible for a skilled user to create rules.</p><p>All this means that no document is too challenging for Vantage to solve. If you have the human skill set, the new advanced designer will give you the tools to show off your expert skills and further developed trained document skills for your business groups.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=3727260&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="http://www.aiseesoft.com/avangate/30p/banner.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Building-out-the-delivery-of-a-Cloud-native-platform-with-flexibility"><a href="#Building-out-the-delivery-of-a-Cloud-native-platform-with-flexibility" class="headerlink" title="Building out the delivery of a Cloud native platform with flexibility"></a>Building out the delivery of a Cloud native platform with flexibility</h2><p>Native Cloud and all the buzzwords associated with the next wave of automation platforms can be mind-numbing for a business user, but have special meaning to the IT architect. To the IT architect team, the platform design is key to any purchase decision. The IT team wants to know they are not locking into any delivery model or working with a platform that is closed off and difficult to integrate with all their other cloud native apps.</p><p>Not to worry, Vantage was built from the very beginning around microservices and containerization. This modern technology approach gives the flexibility for enterprises to choose how or where they want to run their platform. Furthermore, IT architects can be rest assured they don’t need to learn some new deployment model when in fact what is being delivered can fit into their standard operating procedures.</p><p>Today, organizations are looking for both enterprise software as a service (SaaS) to on-premise deployment models that are not going to turn things upside down and will fit into the new delivery modes that they are adopting. That is why in the v2.1.1 (due out end of December) we are making Vantage deployable in on-premise environments using Red Hat® OpenShift®.</p><h2 id="Get-started-today"><a href="#Get-started-today" class="headerlink" title="Get started today!"></a>Get started today!</h2><p>As you can see, ABBYY has accomplished a lot since August 2021. Going into 2022, expect to see much more innovation, with our release cadence being once a quarter. We will continue to focus on advancing our core AI technology while lowering the cost of implementation by focusing on delivering the best low-code &#x2F; no-code IDP platform.</p><p>If you have a trial of Vantage in the Cloud today, you already have access to all these incredible capabilities. If you are just learning about Vantage now and have a project in mind, <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >contact us today <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> for a personalized meeting and demo and then get started with your trial.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Request demo <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/blog/intelligent-document-processing-idp/"  title="Intelligent Document Processing (IDP)">Intelligent Document Processing (IDP) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Intelligent Automation <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Digital Transformation <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> <a class="link"   href="https://www.abbyy.com/blog/robotic-process-automation-rpa/"  title="Robotic Process Automation (RPA)">Robotic Process Automation (RPA) <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static5.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/25718/billgalusha-99x99.png"                      alt="Bill Galusha ABBYY"                ></p><p>Bill Galusha</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4537546&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/4b0a0290ad7df100b77e86839989a75e/products/7_copy_2_2_hdpro.png"                      border="0"                >HD Video Converter Factory Pro</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Like-share-or-repost"><a href="#Like-share-or-repost" class="headerlink" title="Like, share or repost"></a>Like, share or repost</h3><p>Share </p><h4 id="Subscribe-for-blog-updates"><a href="#Subscribe-for-blog-updates" class="headerlink" title="Subscribe for blog updates"></a>Subscribe for blog updates</h4><p>First name*</p><p>E-mail*</p><p>Сountry*</p><p>СountryAfghanistanAland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo (Brazzaville)Congo, (Kinshasa)Cook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong Kong, SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLao PDRLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao, SAR ChinaMacedonia, Republic ofMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoryPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRwandaRéunionSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and GrenadinesSaint-BarthélemySaint-Martin (French part)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and the South Sandwich IslandsSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwan, Republic of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States of AmericaUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic)Viet NamVirgin Islands, USWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaZambiaZimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>I have read and agree with the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Privacy policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> and the <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie policy <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p></li><li><p>I agree to receive email updates from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. such as news related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and technologies, invitations to events and webinars, and information about whitepapers and content related to ABBYY Solutions Ltd. products and services.</p></li></ul><p>I am aware that my consent could be revoked at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link inside any email received from ABBYY Solutions Ltd. or via <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >ABBYY Data Subject Access Rights Form <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Last name</p><p>Query string</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Captcha Score</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Connect with us</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Revolutionize-Your-Paperwork-Unveiling-the-Power-of-ABBYY-Vantage-Version-2-1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Revolutionize-Your-Paperwork-Unveiling-the-</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Optimize Your Website&#39;s Performance Using Advanced Cookiebot Solutions</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/optimize-your-websites-performance-using-advanced-cookiebot-solutions/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/optimize-your-websites-performance-using-advanced-cookiebot-solutions/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.557Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.557Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Optimize-Your-Website’s-Performance-Using-Advanced-Cookiebot-Solutions"><a href="#Optimize-Your-Website’s-Performance-Using-Advanced-Cookiebot-Solutions" class="headerlink" title="Optimize Your Website’s Performance Using Advanced Cookiebot Solutions"></a>Optimize Your Website’s Performance Using Advanced Cookiebot Solutions</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Customer stories <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p>Legal | BPO and Shared Services | eDiscovery | Document Processing</p><h2 id="eDiscovery-Leader-Adds-Advanced-Intelligent-Document-Processing-with-ABBYY"><a href="#eDiscovery-Leader-Adds-Advanced-Intelligent-Document-Processing-with-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="eDiscovery Leader Adds Advanced Intelligent Document Processing with ABBYY"></a>eDiscovery Leader Adds Advanced Intelligent Document Processing with ABBYY</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://content.abbyy.com/-/media/project/abbyy/abbyy/logos-white/en/182212.png?h=40&iar=0&w=120"                      alt="pathner logo"                ></p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Back to Customer stories <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><h2 id="eDiscovery-Leader-Adds-Advanced-Intelligent-Document-Processing-with-ABBYY-1"><a href="#eDiscovery-Leader-Adds-Advanced-Intelligent-Document-Processing-with-ABBYY-1" class="headerlink" title="eDiscovery Leader Adds Advanced Intelligent Document Processing with ABBYY"></a>eDiscovery Leader Adds Advanced Intelligent Document Processing with ABBYY</h2><p>BPO and Shared Services | Document Processing </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/36085/abbyy-nuix-556x303.jpg"                      alt="Costain Transforms Its Finance Department Using ABBYY Content Intelligence"                > </p><h4 id="Customer-Overview"><a href="#Customer-Overview" class="headerlink" title="Customer Overview"></a>Customer Overview</h4><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/36096/nuix-logo_117x56.jpg"                      alt="Nuix"                > </p><table><thead><tr><th>Name</th><th>Nuix</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Headquarters</td><td>Sydney, Australia (Global HQ)</td></tr><tr><td>Industry</td><td>eDiscovery</td></tr><tr><td>Web</td><td><a class="link"   href="https://www.nuix.com/" >www.nuix.com <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></td></tr></tbody></table><p>Nuix began in 2000 with a clear vision: Tame the vast quantities of information involved in eDiscovery with the power to search and manage unstructured data sets of any size. But that data is often trapped in unsearchable documents, so manual assessment of each image file was still necessary—until Nuix automated the task of converting them into searchable documents with ABBYY intelligent document processing technology.</p><h6 id="Challenge"><a href="#Challenge" class="headerlink" title="Challenge"></a>Challenge</h6><p>Inability to process unsearchable documents or digitize handwritten text, which in many cases contains the most valuable information, led to high volume manual review of documents</p><h6 id="Solution"><a href="#Solution" class="headerlink" title="Solution"></a>Solution</h6><p>ABBYY’s IDP solution integrates into the Nuix platform to automatically recognize and convert unsearchable documents into searchable text as part of a project’s workflow, including handwritten text</p><h6 id="Results"><a href="#Results" class="headerlink" title="Results"></a>Results</h6><p>Greater volumes of data are processed without the need for human intervention, enabling key staff with the time and resources to be far more focused on responding to litigation and be more effective in their replies</p><h4 id="Challenge-1"><a href="#Challenge-1" class="headerlink" title="Challenge"></a>Challenge</h4><p>Nuix eDiscovery is the world’s fastest and most scalable electronic discovery platform. As comfortable on a workstation as it is on a server, it’s capable of processing up to 625 gigabytes of unstructured data an hour—up to 500 terabytes per case. Plus, the software directly indexes all unstructured information, regardless of language or file format.</p><p>Nuix eDiscovery helped clients to rapidly search and manage data sets of any size or complexity—enabling them to respond quickly to litigation. But one issue remained to be addressed: the need for review of every document that was in non-searchable format and therefore unavailable for automatic processing within Nuix.</p><p>“We engage proactively with customers,” explained Eddie Sheehy, Nuix’s CEO. “Their feedback is very important to us. And the need to automate the review of non-searchable documents was key. Manual review was costing some clients considerable time and resources.”</p><p>So when their client service representatives advised Nuix of a powerful intelligent document processing solution for making image-based documents discoverable, they were quick to collaborate with ABBYY.</p><p> “ABBYY’s parallel processing of documents in need of OCR is outstanding. On a single server, customers are achieving up to 30,000 pages per hour. ABBYY has brilliant OCR software that works every time.”</p><p> Eddie Sheehy, CEO, Nuix</p><h4 id="Solution-1"><a href="#Solution-1" class="headerlink" title="Solution"></a>Solution</h4><p>Nuix’s team tested the solution—and the software proved a fast fit. Integration was swift and completed within a day. Nuix eDiscovery offered customers the benefit of automated conversion of digital files into searchable formats. “Our goal, always, is a faster, better and smarter eDiscovery process for our customers,” states Eddie Sheehy, Nuix’s CEO. “And towards that end we seek to integrate tools and workflows to streamline the entire eDiscovery process. ABBYY IDP fits that bill.”</p><p>Once deployed, Nuix eDiscovery ingests, examines and makes searchable all relevant unstructured data—making the information easily available for investigation, culling, review and production. Prior to the integration with ABBYY technologies, though, non-searchable PDFs and TIFFs presented customers with a bottleneck.</p><p>Now, however, Nuix workflows automatically extract non-searchable documents from a caseload. ABBYY platform picks up the files, recognizes them, and converts them into a text format. After conversion, a second Nuix workflow uploads the converted files back into the Nuix project, ready to be indexed with the rest of the case data. The entire process runs in the background, is transparent to users. and greatly enhances project efficiency. “ABBYY’s parallel processing of documents in need of OCR is outstanding. On a single server, customers are achieving up to 30,000 pages per hour,” says Eddie Sheehy, Nuix’s CEO. </p><h4 id="Have-a-challenge-Let’s-find-a-solution"><a href="#Have-a-challenge-Let’s-find-a-solution" class="headerlink" title="Have a challenge? Let’s find a solution"></a>Have a challenge? Let’s find a solution</h4><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contact us <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><h4 id="Results-1"><a href="#Results-1" class="headerlink" title="Results"></a>Results</h4><p>The savings in time and resources for Nuix’s customers are considerable. Greater volumes of data can be processed without the need for human intervention—enabling key staff to be far more focused on responding to litigation and more effective in their replies.</p><p>For Nuix, too, the benefits are multiple. “The added value that ABBYY brings is significant. From customer satisfaction to increasing our competitiveness, ABBYY gives us an edge,” states Sheehy. “Not only can we perform OCR for customers, Nuix can also add converted data to the index on the fly—no re-indexing necessary.”</p><p>“We’ve been working together for many years,” says Sheehy “and have 35 joint clients in 15 countries ranging from ASIC, ATO and Deloitte based in Australia to SFO (UK) and SEC (US). ABBYY has brilliant IDP software that works every time.”</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >More about ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Find your ABBYY office <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4729320&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/f7f07e7dab09533bc71247a5b29a7373/products/2_iDeviceMessageBox.png"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Ready-to-talk-to-an-expert"><a href="#Ready-to-talk-to-an-expert" class="headerlink" title="Ready to talk to an expert?"></a>Ready to talk to an expert?</h3><p>We’d love to help you along your automation journey.</p><p><a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Contact us <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Optimize-Your-Website’s-Performance-Using-Advanced-Cookiebot-Solutions&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Optimize-Your-Website’s-Performance-Using-Advanced</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Navigating the Future of ARB in Finance – Unveiling Strategies From ABBYY White Paper on Digital Transformation</title>
    <link href="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/navigating-the-future-of-arb-in-finance-unveiling-strategies-from-abbyy-white-paper-on-digital-transformation/"/>
    <id>https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/navigating-the-future-of-arb-in-finance-unveiling-strategies-from-abbyy-white-paper-on-digital-transformation/</id>
    <published>2024-08-21T07:11:23.549Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-22T07:11:23.549Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Navigating-the-Future-of-ARB-in-Finance-–-Unveiling-Strategies-From-ABBYY-White-Paper-on-Digital-Transformation"><a href="#Navigating-the-Future-of-ARB-in-Finance-–-Unveiling-Strategies-From-ABBYY-White-Paper-on-Digital-Transformation" class="headerlink" title="Navigating the Future of ARB in Finance – Unveiling Strategies From ABBYY White Paper on Digital Transformation"></a>Navigating the Future of ARB in Finance – Unveiling Strategies From ABBYY White Paper on Digital Transformation</h2><p>Whitepaper</p><h2 id="Schaffung-von-Grundlagen-fur-die-Digitale-Transformation-in-der-Kreditoren­buch­haltung"><a href="#Schaffung-von-Grundlagen-fur-die-Digitale-Transformation-in-der-Kreditoren­buch­haltung" class="headerlink" title="Schaffung von Grundlagen für die Digitale Transformation in der Kreditoren­buch­haltung"></a>Schaffung von Grundlagen für die Digitale Transformation in der Kreditoren­buch­haltung</h2><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static1.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/21563/33b-ap-levelresearch-de-262x340.png"                      alt="Whitepaper „Schaffung von Grundlagen für die digitale Transformation in der Kreditorenbuchhaltung“"                ></p><h3 id="Gewinnen-Sie-mehr-Effizienz-und-Kontrolle-durch-die-Transformation-der-Kreditoren­buch­haltung"><a href="#Gewinnen-Sie-mehr-Effizienz-und-Kontrolle-durch-die-Transformation-der-Kreditoren­buch­haltung" class="headerlink" title="Gewinnen Sie mehr Effizienz und Kontrolle durch die Transformation der Kreditoren­buch­haltung."></a>Gewinnen Sie mehr Effizienz und Kontrolle durch die Transformation der Kreditoren­buch­haltung.</h3><p>Viele Führungskräfte beginnen die digitale Transformation ihres Unternehmens im Finanzbereich, wo sie zahlreiche Vorteile wie mehr Effizienz und Kontrolle, eine höhere Transparenz und Kosteneinsparungen erzielen können. Dieses Whitepaper vermittelt ein grundlegendes Verständnis der digitalen Transformation in der Kreditorenbuchhaltung.</p><p>In dem Whitepaper „Schaffung von Grundlagen für die digitale Transformation in der Kreditorenbuchhaltung“ beschreibt Levvel Research, wie die Automatisierung der Kreditorenbuchhaltung Unternehmen dabei helfen kann, im heutigen digitalen Geschäftsumfeld erfolgreicher denn je zu werden.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://store.massmailsoftware.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=1300375&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/dc87c13749315c7217cdc4ac692e704c/banera_for_partners-15_%281%29.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h3 id="Jetzt-herunterladen"><a href="#Jetzt-herunterladen" class="headerlink" title="Jetzt herunterladen!"></a>Jetzt herunterladen!</h3><p>Die digitale Transformation wird häufig mit kundenorientierten Funktionen in Verbindung gebracht. Bei internen Prozessen wie der Kreditorenbuchhaltung jedoch können Initiativen zur digitalen Transformation die Produktivität steigern, tiefer gehende datengestützte Erkenntnisse liefern und neue Möglichkeiten erschließen.</p><p><strong>Über Levvel Research</strong><br>Ein Forschungs- und Beratungsunternehmen, das sich schwerpunktmäßig mit innovativen Technologien befasst. Seine Experten stellen gezielte Inhalte bereit, um die Prozessanforderungen wettbewerbsorientierter Unternehmen zu erfüllen. Das Ziel dabei ist, die Erträge zu maximieren und die mit Technologieinvestitionen verbundenen Risiken zu minimieren.</p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://estore.winxdvd.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=4612444&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://www.winxdvd.com/affiliate/new-banner/pt-728x90.jpg"                      border="0"                ></a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h2 id="Danke-fur-Ihr-Interesse-an-ABBYY"><a href="#Danke-fur-Ihr-Interesse-an-ABBYY" class="headerlink" title="Danke für Ihr Interesse an ABBYY."></a>Danke für Ihr Interesse an ABBYY.</h2><p><a class="link"   href="https://digital.abbyy.com/hubfs/content/white-paper-levvel-research-digital-transformation-in-ap-de.pdf"  title="Whitepaper herunterladen">Whitepaper herunterladen <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> </p><p><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://static4.abbyy.com/abbyycommedia/31652/factoids-027-77x77.svg"                      alt="Factoids 027 77X77"                ></p><!-- affiliate ads begin --><p><a href="https://secure.2checkout.com/order/checkout.php?PRODS=11224199&QTY=1&AFFILIATE=108875&CART=1"><img                       lazyload                     src="/images/loading.svg"                     data-src="https://secure.avangate.com/images/merchant/e09fdffe648a30658a9657bbed7b2388/products/copy_boxshot_lyricvideo.png"                      border="0"                >Lyric Video Creator Professional Version</a></p><!-- affiliate ads end --><h4 id="Haben-Sie-Fragen-Kontaktieren-Sie-uns"><a href="#Haben-Sie-Fragen-Kontaktieren-Sie-uns" class="headerlink" title="Haben Sie Fragen? Kontaktieren Sie uns."></a>Haben Sie Fragen? <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Kontaktieren Sie uns. <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a></h4><h4 id="Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form"><a href="#Get-your-copy-by-filling-in-the-form" class="headerlink" title="Get your copy by filling in the form."></a>Get your copy by filling in the form.</h4><p>Vorname*</p><p>Nachname*</p><p>E-Mail*</p><p>Land*</p><p>LandAfghanistanAland-InselnAlbanienAlgerienAmerikanisch-SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarktisAntigua und BarbudaArgentinienArmenienArubaAustralienÖsterreichAserbaidschanBahamasBahrainBangladeschBarbadosBelgienBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBolivienBonaireBosnien und HerzegowinaBotsuanaBouvetinselBrasilienBritisches Territorium im Indischen OzeanBritische JungferninselnBrunei DarussalamBulgarienBurkina FasoBurundiKambodschaKamerunKanadaCabo VerdeKaimaninselnZentralafrikanische RepublikTschadChileChinaWeihnachtsinselKokosinselnKolumbienKomorenRepublik KongoDemokratische Republik KongoCookinselnCosta RicaKroatienCuraçaoZypernTschechischeCôte d`IvoireDänemarkDschibutiDominicaDominikanische RepublikEcuadorÄgyptenEl SalvadorÄquatorialguineaEritreaEstlandÄthiopienFalklandinselnFäröerFidschiFinnlandFrankreichFranzösisch-GuayanaFranzösisch-PolynesienFranzösische SüdgebieteGabunGambiaGeorgienDeutschlandGhanaGibraltarGriechenlandGrönlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard und die McDonaldinselnVatikanstadtHondurasHongkongUngarnIslandIndienIndonesienIrakIrlandIsle of ManIsraelITJamaikaJapanJerseyJordanienKasachstanKeniaKiribatiSüdkoreaKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLettlandLibanonLesothoLiberiaLibyenLiechtensteinLitauenLuxemburgMacauMazedonienMadagaskarMalawiMalaysiaMaledivenMaliMaltaMarshall-InselnMartiniqueMauretanienMauritiusMayotteMexikoMikronesienMoldawienMonacoMongoleiMontenegroMontserratMarokkoMosambikMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNiederlandeNiederländische AntillenNeukaledonienNeuseelandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolkinselNördliche MarianenNorwegenOmanPakistanPalauPalästinaPanamaPapua-NeuguineaParaguayPeruPhilippinenPitcairnPolenPortugalPuerto RicoKatarRumänienRuandaWiedervereinigungSt. HelenaSt. Kitts und NevisSt. LuciaSaint-Pierre und MiquelonSt. Vincent und die GrenadinenSaint-BarthélemySaint Martin (französischer Teil)SamoaSan MarinoSão Tomé und PríncipeSaudi-ArabienSenegalSerbienSeychellenSierra LeoneSingapurSt. MartinSlowakeiSlowenienSalomonenSüdafrikaSüdgeorgien und die Südlichen SandwichinselnSüdsudanSpanienSri LankaSurinameSpitzbergen (Norwegen)SwasilandSchwedenSchweizTaiwanTadschikistanTansaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad und TobagoTunesienTürkeiTurks- und CaicosinselnTuvaluUgandaUkraineVereinigte Arabische EmirateGroßbritannienUSAUruguayKleinere amerikanische ÜberseeinselnUsbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamAmerikanische JungferninselnWallis und FutunaWestsaharaSambiaSimbabwe</p><ul><li><p>Ich habe die <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Datenschutzerklärung <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> und die <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Cookie-Richtlinie <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a> gelesen und bin damit einverstanden.*</p></li><li><p>Ich bin damit einverstanden, dass ABBYY Solutions Ltd. mich per E-Mail über Neuigkeiten zu Produkten und Technologien von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. informiert sowie Einladungen zu Veranstaltungen und Webinaren und Informationen über Whitepaper und Inhalte zu Produkten und Dienstleistungen von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. an mich sendet.</p></li></ul><p>Mir ist bekannt, dass ich meine Einwilligung jederzeit widerrufen kann, indem ich auf den Link zur Abmeldung in einer von ABBYY Solutions Ltd. erhaltenen E-Mail klicke oder über das <a class="link"   href="https://tools.techidaily.com/abbyy/products/" >Datensubjekt-Zugriffsformular von ABBYY <i class="fa-regular fa-arrow-up-right-from-square fa-sm"></i></a>.</p><p>Referrer</p><p>Anrede</p><p>Academic Title</p><p>Query string</p><p>Stellen Sie eine Frage, oder beschreiben Sie Ihr Anliegen</p><p>Business Scenario Temp</p><p>City</p><p>Product Interest Temp</p><p>GA Client ID</p><p>ITM Source</p><p>UTM Campaign Name</p><p>UTM Content</p><p>UTM Medium</p><p>UTM Source</p><p>GDPR Consent Note</p><p>Page URL</p><p>Vernetzen Sie sich mit uns</p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-format="autorelaxed"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="1223367746"></ins></p><p><ins class="adsbygoogle"     style="display:block"     data-ad-client="ca-pub-7571918770474297"     data-ad-slot="8358498916"     data-ad-format="auto"     data-full-width-responsive="true"></ins></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;Navigating-the-Future-of-ARB-in-Finance-–-Unveiling-Strategies-From-ABBYY-White-Paper-on-Digital-Transformation&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Navigatin</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="abbyy" scheme="https://solve-popular.techidaily.com/categories/abbyy/"/>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
